e
[Music]
well good morning good afternoon and
good evening and welcome to living Mana
Church it is such a privilege to be able
to worship with you guys together today
here at Living Mana uh we are just
behind the scenes preparing everything
and in preparation for that one of the
things that I want to take the time to
do is just thank you all so much for
sharing every single broadcast that we
do here for Sabbath school and divine
worship service we cannot thank you
enough for joining in the message and
helping to share the Three Angels
message and we just want to thank you
again for being our digital disciples
our numbers continue to grow on our
living Mana YouTube channel and I want
to say special Welcome to our living
Mana YouTube channel family shout out to
you guys today as well as to our power
of the Lamb you guys are always you were
the Forefront in helping to build this
side of the channel for living manner
church and so we thank you so much for
being there and holding it down strong
and uh we asking once again that you'll
please make sure you share of this live
um I want to say Greetings if this is
your first time watching uh with us
today and you able to catch us right now
for the beginning of Sabbath School uh
please put that one in the chat um you
know our our members and even regulars
are always here to say welcome and give
shout outs to you guys and of course we
always leave the roll call to our dear
uh p uh brother Terry who is our prayer
team lead director and who will also be
bringing our fresh bread today um I
always tell you Pastor Myers never
leaves us without an Avenue and a person
anointed to bring fresh bread and today
is our own and special brother Terry so
we are looking forward to what God has
downloaded into him so right now I'm
going to give a couple shout outs myself
um aana toas is always in the building
making sure she shares a quicko Nicole C
I see you in the building blessing Joy
you're in here of course I see brother
Terry God bless you my brother uh
Christina uh Taj I see you here as well
and all of you please make sure you
greet one another in the chat uh right
now living Mana uh kids is they're
actually in process of having their
service which started at 11:30 Central
Standard Time and for those parents that
would still like to have your kids be a
part of it I'm going to ask
talking about Sabbath school and we are
preparing for a rebroadcast of what
Pastor Myers did with and sister pante
back to the basics one as I said to you
before um you know repetition deep their
impression and so where we are in
Earth's history we can definitely see
the clear signs that the Lord's return
is truly emminent and so while we can
Garner oil while we can Garner bread
please let us gather it please take
advantage of the opportunity for us
don't take it for granted that we will
always be here while we can still get
oil please gather it and please share it
do not be a gatekeeper please share the
link so that others can gather bread and
buy oil while it is freely available by
the power of the Holy Spirit through
living Mana Church uh we're asking your
continued prayers with Pastor Meyers and
sister tante um U S Mrs Myers and her
husband and their entire family Sean's
beautiful wife Veronica and their
amazing children please keep the Myers
family in your prayer as you know this
next this coming week um they will be
having the official memorial service for
him we'll give more details about that
um doing Divine service so in the
meantime uh sit back relax get your pen
paper whatever writing utensils you have
and prepare for the rebroadcast of back
to the basics part one see you
soon evident that a lot of our people
are confused on prophetic events right
and um we are
looking at current events and allowing
that to dictate what we believe about
prophecy versus looking at
prophecy and uh allowing that
to uh determine what in current events
is actually part of Prophecy and what
isn't right and so
um you know we're doing this series
because there is just a lot of confusion
out out there about prophecy
um and we need to go back to the basics
some very basic Elementary
things that uh you know was long
understood uh within adventism is
now you know up in question in in the
minds of of are being mingled
with human prophecy that's all I can
call it human prophecies and not the
biblical prophecy yeah yeah so um we
want wanted to uh take these next uh
several weeks and you know just get down
into prophecies in the Book of
Revelation in the Book of Daniel um we
want to look particularly at the
prophecy of Daniel chapter 11 vers 40 to
45 which I don't know how much we're
going to get into that today but we want
to simplify these prophecies right today
we're going to be dealing with the
deadly wound and um even if you have
questions you can you know um put those
questions in the chat yes we're going to
be taking your questions um and comments
this is Sabbath school so we want
everyone to feel like they have a voice
or you know they can that we're
dialoguing and studying together yeah I
am his student you guys are all his
students um and it is my job and goal to
keep this back to the basics very basic
so we don't lose anyone that there's no
gaps I saw somebody last night that said
I'm going to have my 14 old sitting
right next to me so I noted that and was
like okay we we I know we have one
14-year-old that's watching this morning
there could be many more um but we want
the 14 yearold the 28y old the 50 Year
everyone every age to understand so that
there's just no gaps um so what's
happening what we see happening now uh
within the church um with a lot of
misinformation that in regards to
prophecy um won't happen at the level
that it's happening at this time yeah
our prayerful goal yeah today my sermon
is actually going to be kind of
piggybacking off of what we discussed in
Sabbath School um but it's going to take
it you know a lot further okay but um we
really want to encourage you to to take
notes we want to encourage you to you
know really follow along carefully um
we're going to take a a huge subject and
again try to simplify it so we're not
necessarily moving in chronological
order uh in terms of going through
various prophecies we're going to kind
of be gonna kind of you know deal with
various issues where I see a lot of
confusion happening and um and that's
over the next several weeks of course so
um that's kind of the the plan of of of
how we
proceed okay but today we're talking
about the deadly wound the healing of
the deadly wound we're going to see why
this subject is so important all right
so let's pray all right let's pray
Heavenly
Father we thank you Lord for uh your
mercy and Grace we thank you for your
kindness Your Love towards us Lord and
we thank you for everyone that has
joined us today we ask Lord that today
as we study this this topic of the
deadly wound Lord that you would give us
understanding that you would give us
wisdom and that you would open our eyes
Lord that we may see this we pray in
jesus' name amen and amen amen
amen um I will be constantly looking to
see if you guys have questions as he's
going if you if you guys need say hey
time out to review that go again so you
know just put that in the chat um if
you're needing him to slow down I'll try
to slow him down as well so okay not
saying you won't go slow
and and I already see a question by Lisa
that I want to I want to address real
quickly um so her question is uh why do
you think people are getting off track
when it comes to prophecy and current
world events and uh if you haven't seen
my sermon entitled uh sign confusion I
would strongly recommend that you go and
watch that that message because it deals
with this very subject sign confusion
that we have become so
um trained right to look for signs
obviously I think we we want Jesus to
come right right we we we want to see
these things
finally wrap up and yet there's a
there's a way there's a dangerous
there's a danger
in well go ahead attempting to make
everything a sign
and we have seen this becoming more and
more of a problem within our church over
the last few years and listen when
people are are hooked on a
sign it doesn't matter what you say
they're going to believe it until it's
too late they see that the sign that
they thought was a sign is is is
incorrect and people either leave the
faith or become more um
know less believing in in the Bible and
the prophecies and we've seen that
happen over the
last three or four years we've seen this
happened several times in a major way I
think the sermon you did two weeks ago
cleared that up in my mind I mean it was
you know and so but maybe many of them
probably may have seen it may have not
um um but now we're going to go in a
little bit deeper and just fill that in
even more yeah
because there are signs that we should
be looking for but the Bible
clearly yeah tells us what those what
those are what those signs and we don't
have to go search for new we don't make
up the signs you know and um and the
signs are very clear and I'm using this
kind of in a joking way but there's not
signs before the signs yeah I just made
that up yeah the because I hear that a
lot yeah or like the test before the
test the test before the test but I just
made that up the sign before the sign to
understand right we need to understand
that
um if God is love which we believe he is
then he is not going to leave us to
figure things out for ourselves that's
why he's given us prophecy so that we
can understand right so that we can
understand what is coming to pass he
says behold I tell you before it come to
pass that when it comes to pass you
might believe that I'm he so if there
are things that are supposed to be
happening that God has not told
us then that puts God's character right
on trial question right in question
because now I had to go figure something
out that was not clearly revealed in the
Bible that was not clearly foretold in
the Bible something that is detrimental
to my salvation and I had to you know go
figure it out why wasn't it in the Bible
right God everything that is necessary
for our
Salvation God has revealed through the
Bible and he has Amplified it in the
spirit of Prophecy right so it is
already there in the bible let me let me
mention another Point here because
something that a lot of people do a lot
of Adventists do this
right we tend to go to the Lesser
light first right to determine what the
greater light says yes and every time
that is done we're going going to read
the Lesser light in the wrong light okay
so go in deeper and explain that okay so
exactly what you're saying what I mean
is yeah what I mean is
this the spirit of Prophecy was given to
us to amplify what the word of God said
right alen white says that clearly over
and over and over again right she says
the word of God first right so her work
is simply to accentuate if you will or
to to uh uh I don't want to use the term
bring Clarity because the word of God is
already clear right but it just gives us
a lens through which we can get a
greater understanding right but what
happens
is why a lot of people will go to the
spirit of Prophecy first and and get
their understanding of Prophecy from
that thinking well what she says is not
in the Bible so I have to go to her
right when what she says is in the Bible
right but because we haven't gone to the
Bible
First we go to her writings right and
then we begin to see or read things in
out of
context that actually contradict what
the Bible says right so bottom
line with the word of God right the word
of God is the big
bring Clarity for us okay so just put a
one in the chat if you understand that
Bible First Spirit of Prophecy so let's
go ahead oh gonna say a second okay just
didn't say that word so let's go ahead
and get into this issue of the deadly
wound and I want to um Aton you have the
Bible open so I'm going to ask you to
read right we're going to go to
Revelation chapter 13 verses 1-4
Revelation chap 13 veres 1 through 4
sorry I have to change it to the King
James I had it on the Amplified all
right all right and I stood upon the
sand of the sea and saw a beast rise up
out of the sea having seven heads and 10
horns and upon his horns 10 crowns and
upon his heads the same the name of
blasphemy and the Beast which I saw was
like into a leopard and his feet were as
the feet of a bear and his mouth as the
mouth of a lion and the dragon gave him
his power and his seat and great
Authority and I saw one of his heads as
it were wounded to death and his deadly
wound was healed and all the world
wondered after the Beast okay so you
could pause right there and uh what I'm
gonna do right I'm going to um because
our subject is the deadly wound okay I'm
going to to
assume that you understand that this
first
Beast represents the paper power during
the Dark Ages okay so that's pretty
common knowledge put a one in the chat
if you're aware if you're like yeah
pastor we got that I'm trying to keep
this as basic as I can right but there's
there's just stuff I can't really go
through because of
time so I'm not going to go through you
know what these uh uh the lion the bear
the leopard all of that is in Daniel
chapter 7 right and basically it all
points us to the papal power now the
Bible tells us that this papal power was
to rule for
1,260 years and Aton I want want want
you to read Revelation 13:7 Revelation
13 and verse 7 let's see what that says
and it was given unto him to make war
with the Saints and to overcome them and
power was given him over all kindreds
and tongues and Nations okay so this
happens did you read uh I stopped at
three I didn't read four five or six all
right and just go ahead and read verse
five as
well and there was given unto him a
mouth speaking great things and
blasphemies and power was given unto him
to continue 40 and2 months okay so for
42 months or
1,260 years am I losing you you're not
losing me but as you it's funny as you
said that because I'm just thinking of
someone that's
never even you know heard and I know I
even heard that the math behind it okay
that right there might be so a little
confusing so okay this 42 months right
uh it it is a it is equivalent to 1,26
days in prophetic time a day is equal to
a year so this is a time period of
1,260
years aka the Dark Ages okay when the
papal power ruled with authority they
were ruling over the Nations they were
not ruling with the Nations it wasn't a
partnership where it was like some of
the Nations they were ruling over the
Nations this is very important to
understand y'all they were ruling over
the nation
right and um what did they do during
this time well they had persecuting
power they thought to change times and
laws that's Daniel
7:25 speaking of the same little horn
power it says he would think to change
times and laws they would be given into
his hand until the time times and a half
um and he would think to change times
and law so during this 1260 years the
papacy in its strength
so listen carefully to that y'all the
papacy in its in its
strength okay
were
persecuting they
were exercising power over the Nations
and they changed times and
laws the Bible tells us that this Beast
receives a deadly wound a deadly wound
so let me
um give me one second here
so this deadly
wound when was it given it was
given in
1798 one in the chat if you if you're
following me so far the deadly wound
1798 that is the end of the
1,260 years right
this deadly wound is given in that the
papacy loses its power to persecute
right we know during the French
Revolution right after the French
Revolution
1798 uh General birth year uh abolishes
the Papal States and this is the deadly
wound
now here is where we
begin to really focusing on this idea of
the deadly wound the Bible says that the
deadly wound
was
healed so we know that we're looking for
the healing of this wound so what is the
healing of so them losing power okay
yeah we're gonna go back to the when
they lost power that was a wound that
was the wound okay okay they lost power
that's the wound now the Bible is
telling us that the deadly wound is
going to be
healed okay so we're looking for a time
where that we're looking for a time
where the wound heals so here's my
question what happens when the wound
heals according to the text read
Revelation 13 verse4 again what happens
when the wound heals and they worshiped
the dragon which gave power unto the
Beast and they worshiped the Beast
saying who is like unto the actually
verse three end of verse three okay
um the end of verse three
um and his deadly wound was healed and
all the world wanded after the Beast all
right so let let's let's break this
down the Bible tells us that something
happens when the deadly wound is healed
and that thing that happens
is come on y'all put it in the chat what
is it that
happens
all the
world does what
I'm waiting to see all the world does
what all right I'm still gonna wait I'm
just gonna take my time and and wait I I
I need y'all to see this and catch this
because most people M very good y'all
all the world
wonders after the Beast
all right so let's try this again
there's a delay that's why it took so
long that they didn't know does does
some of the world Wonder after the Beast
yes or
no does some of the world Wonder after
the
Beast does half of the world Wonder
after the
Beast all of the
world the Bible says that the whole
world wonders after the Beast so one of
the ways in which we can know whether
the deadly wound has been healed or not
is simply by asking the question is the
whole world wondering after the Beast so
that's my question right now y'all can I
just say this real
quick because I think this here this
point here is something that Satan has
used to try to confuse the church and
the world really when it comes to Bible
prophecy and what the Bible saying
because there's people there's
non-adventist who might know this
scripture I've heard this scripture And
when they see what's going on in the
world where this pandemic has taken over
all of the world and everybody is you
know every country is trying to get
their citizens to be vaccinated and
everybody had lockdowns on some level
you know they could like just take that
even though this terminology has nothing
to do with that yeah but they take that
because they're not understanding yeah
that this uh Beast is not the CDC or
whatever you know that or you know
health organizations from around the
world does that make sense yeah so let
me let me let me talk about that real
quick all right and you guys we not talk
we're not going vaccine or nonvaccine
discussion today okay we're not but I
want to show you something but there's a
lot of confusion and it's intermingled
with that okay the Bible says that the
whole world not half the world not
there's not going to be a conflict
within the world over this issue and
right now y'all there's a conflict in
the world over vaccination versus
nonvaccination the whole world isn't on
the same page in fact the whole world is
very divided on this issue right you see
what I'm saying true that can't be a
fulfillment or a precursor of what's
happened in Revelation 133 because when
this happens everybody right is is on
the same page right everybody except
who everybody
except the
remnant everybody except those who keep
the Commandments of God and have the
testimony of Jesus it's not great
division in the world there's not you
know Waring within the world over
whether we should do this or whether we
should do that no the whole world is on
the same page it's not one political
party it's not one political party
against another the whole world is on
the same page and once we can understand
that the whole world will be on the same
page that's going to put some things
into perspective for that's gonna Force
us to start asking some pretty serious
questions
right how is it that the whole world
gets on the same page now watch this
you can't get the whole world on the
same page about
anything this is true just look at
what's going on right now right look at
the issue of the vaccine I like we said
the whole world's divided on that right
The Whole World's divided on mass the
whole world is divided on politics the
whole world is divided on a whole lot of
things right just think about the
different
factions you have in the world you have
Christians and within Christianity you
have all different kinds of
denominations you have
atheists you have Muslims you have
radical Muslims you have uh uh Buddhists
you have new
agers right you have left you have right
how in the
world how in the world does the whole
world get on the same page in wondering
after the
Beast all right if y'all have follow me
so far just give me one because what I
want you to see right here is that it is
obvious that the deadly wound is not yet
healed
because atheists aren't wondering after
the Beast Muslims aren't wondering after
the Beast
right uh uh
um evangelicals at the time we're not
wondering after the Beast either
evangelicals are kind
of you know confused's confus they
wouldn't say that that they were
wondering you know that they were
following that power yeah the whole
world is not wandering after the Beast
so if the whole world is not wandering
after the Beast it means that the deadly
wound has not yet been healed I know I'm
hammering this point but it's a basic
it's important it's important to
understand failure to understand this
point is what is leading to so much
confusion right when you hear people say
the world is wondering after the Beast
nah nope the world is not wondering
after the Beast that we can go down the
list of people who do not
care what the papacy is saying do not
care what the pope is saying so the
question is what is it that then brings
about the entire world to be on the same
page there's a question that I think is
is could be asked it says would it be
safe to say the wound is has started to
be healed all right so that's a good
question yeah I'm gonna use a sports
analogy all
right so let's use a sport basketball
somebody gets injured they're out of the
game okay the healing process starts
immediately but guess
what they can't get back in the game
until they're fully healed okay true
true right so they're not in the game
they can be on the sidelines they're
watching the you know they're not back
to their former power right okay in in
order for this wound to be healed the
power it had during the dark h must be
restored meaning it is persecuting again
it is changing times and laws again do
you understand what I'm saying right
it's gone back to its former power but
something has to empower that something
has to has to happen something pretty
big must happen in order for
the whole world to wonder after the
Beast and for the whole world to wonder
after the Beast it means the deadly
wound must be
healed okay this is I'm trying to keep
it as basic as I proba as I possibly can
the whole world y'all let me just say it
again you can go down the list of
various religions various groups of
people atheists secularists uh uh
Communists who are not wondering after
the Beast therefore the deadly wound
cannot yet be healed because that's not
happening
okay
now I want to go to Revelation Chapter
13 Verse
8 okay let let me pause for a second I'm
gonna address this uh so uh better life
says at cop 26 in November one the
deadly wound the deadly wound will
officially be healed all the world
leaders will inaugurate the PO as
official leader of the world all
right so I want y'all to
mark that date okay and I'm not putting
anyone on spot here but I'm just going
to ask you to Mark November 1st because
here's what I'm going to show you guys
right it
is I don't I'm I'm not even sure how how
how to say this right I think you should
be very clear but but let me say this
even
if even if
somehow these leaders said the pope is
the official leader of the world right
whatever that
means are atheists going to be like well
I guess they're right hope you are now
our leader and yes we want to keep
Sunday are atheists going to do
that our Muslims going to do that our
Muslims going to do that so this
November 1st so we're looking at a
little little a week less than or a
month and a week because we're almost
October 1 so are Muslims gonna do this
are are radical Muslims going to do this
right uh radical are are the terrorists
right who are willing to blow themselves
up willing to uh you know to kill
themselves for their faith are they
going to suddenly be like oh well some
somebody said the pope is a leader so
y'all need to understand this right in
order for the whole
world in order for the whole world to
unite listen to me y'all it's going to
take a
miracle it's going to take a miracle
nothing short of a miracle so people say
oh when people feel that their lives are
in danger that's going to unite the the
whole world well look we got Co right
now we co is happening right now and and
our people uniting saying we've got a
grave threat that is threatening
Humanity let's all come together and go
to church on Sunday
no what you find is they're using some
of that terminology of let's all come
together for the better good of the but
but it's but it's not happening no it's
not happening and it's not saying well
we need to serve God and and return back
to God exactly there's there's no call
for let's go worship on Sunday there's
no there's no religious spiritual or
religious call at all yeah exactly so
what we need to understand is that
something miraculous please listen to
what I just said something miraculous so
so is bad weather gonna lead atheists to
say yeah we need to worship God on
Sunday no
no it's bad we going to lead radical
Islam
or moderate
Islam or Hindus or anybody else to say
yeah we need to go they're probably will
be like well you know what this is Allah
bringing judgment upon the world because
Christians won't convert to
Islam everybody's gonna put it in their
particular context right you you in
other words you guys we got to we got to
allow the Bible to tell us what it's
this reason right we're like oh it's
this oh it's gonna be that oh November
one that's when it's gonna happen three
years ago it was
September it was right it was September
23rd it was actually my birthday that's
right it was I September 23rd Sunday law
Pope is going to be instituted as a
leader of the world September 23rd and
what happens is the more we do this the
more we look like we don't know what
we're talking about right and I can say
that that comment that that person made
and that belief that this person
believes is not um a very popular
well-known belief within adventism on
November 1 that the pope is gonna con
okay I've seen it before okay well
people are saying it believe so listen
y'all this is not I'm not calling
anybody here popular very popular it
it's making its rounds okay right it's
making its rounds so what I'm saying is
this when we don't allow the Bible to to
demonstrate to us what it is that's
supposed to happen MH we begin reading
into the Bible and reading into prophecy
look this date this is going to happen
and that is the that's how it's going to
happen that's how it's going to unfold
watch this let's go to Revelation 13 and
I want you to notice we're in Revelation
13 I want you to notice verse
13 verse 13 and verse 14 verse 13 and
verse 14 going to tell us plainly plain
watch and he do great wonders so that he
maketh the fire come down from heaven on
the earth in the sight of men and
deceiveth them that dwell on the Earth
by the means of those Miracles which he
had power to do in the sight of the
Beast saying to them that dwell on the
earth that they should make no that they
should make an image to the Beast which
had the wound by a sword and did live
all right so I need you to I need you to
check this out y'all in Revelation 13 we
are clearly told what it is that leads
to the setting up of the image of the
Beast so and he doeth great
wonders so
that he maketh Fire come down from
heaven on the earth in the sight of men
and deceive them that dwell on the Earth
by the means of those What miracles
remember what I said earlier it will
take a miracle to bring the whole world
together that's what it's going to take
nothing less y'all nothing natural not
someone saying the pope is a leader of
the world not someone saying the pope is
a leader of the world because if we're
not listening to the the some ones the
some ones who are telling us take the
vaccine or the someone who are telling
us don't take the vaccine what makes
what makes us think the whole world is
going to listen to someone telling us
hey we think the pope should be the
leader of the world so you want to go
into the Miracles now I mean like what
that Mir so what is the Mir what is the
miracle that brings the whole world
together and someone said this a little
bit earlier we have to let the
Bible interpret for us the news and not
the news interpret for us the Bible and
that's what a lot of people are doing
they're looking at the news so I
mentioned it last night when Jerusalem
was was uh re when Israel was
reestablished as a nation there were
administ who were like well look it's
happening on the news and they went back
to the Bible to try to see where this
fit into Bible
prophecy they were allowing the news to
interpret prophecy and that's what we do
often we see something happening and and
and it's a you know it's like a drug I I
I I might say that there's a real to
look look and that's why I did that
sermon about signs right sign confusion
because people get caught up on signs
listen you get ratings when you talk
about signs right I was looking at at at
uh two two Adventist preachers right and
one of them was talking about this is on
YouTube one of them was talking
about how to walk like
Jesus 4,000 views 4,000 views how to
walk like Jesus the other one Sunday law
right around the corner like 100,000
views a and and it shows where our
appetite
is what is that
Miracle what is that fire that Satan
causes or that this that that causes all
men not some of the world but the whole
world to make an image to the Beast
listen y'all the image of the Beast is
not just in the United States of
America they that dwell on the Earth are
going to make this image it's the whole
world and again I'm asking you
what Miracle could possibly bring about
the whole world coming on the same page
well let me read to you a statement from
no no no no no I'm going to go to the
Bible First I want you to know this
second Thessalonians chap 1 verse 7 and
8 the Bible says and to you who are
troubled rest with us when the Lord
Jesus shall be revealed from heaven with
his mighty Angels listen to this in
flaming fire taking Vengeance on them
that know not God and that obey not the
gospel of our Lord Jesus Christ so let
me ask you a question when Jesus comes
at
tante what is he coming with according
to the text let read it
again and to you who are troubled rest
with us when the Lord Jesus shall be
revealed from heaven with the with his
mighty angels in flaming
fire taking Vengeance on them that know
not what is he coming with he's coming
in what in fire with fire and fire is
gonna be coming from the
sky the Bible says in Revelation 13
that's a miracle he doeth great Wonders
that he makes
Fire come from the sky now come on y'all
as as Adventists we know that the sign
of Fire coming from the sky is connected
with the second coming of Jesus if
you're with me just raise your hand I
know I can't see you but just raise your
hand pastor we following you give me a
one yes we got you we see it we know
that when in the days of Noah water came
from the sky at the second coming fire
fire comes from the sky
s the miracle that convinces the whole
world is fire coming from the sky what
does that fire coming from the sky point
us to it points us to the fact that
Satan himself let me read 2 Corinthians
11:14 and no Marvel for Satan himself is
transformed into an angel of Light let
me ask a question you know what that
word light means in the Greek the Greek
is the word FAL F hos and it
means
fire Satan will come as an angel as an
angel of
fire and that's gonna
imitating Jesus
Christ watch this Exodus 24:17 the sight
of the glory of the Lord was like
devouring fire
what does the Lord look like fire what
is he surrounded in fire when he comes
again what's going to happen fire it's
going to fall from the sky what is Satan
going to do he's going to make it
appear that Jesus has come now let me
ask a question and the world will come
together is Jesus a
Buddhist no is Jesus a Muslim
no is
Jesus uh a new Ager no no no
no for an atheist seeing is what
believing seeing is
believing what people don't understand
is
this at the end of
time there's not going to be any
Muslims they're not going to be any
atheists they're not going to be any
nonbelievers they're not going to be uh
uh people of different religions because
everybody is going to be
converted under the of the counterfeit
appearing of Jesus Christ in other words
when this counterfeit appearing happens
everybody's going to see that they were
wrong in their that they were wrong in
their
religion whoa the Christians had
right it wasn't Krishna it wasn't
Muhammad that came it was
Jesus and if it's Jesus that's come back
for us seeing is believing how can we
deny this
miracle and this is such a blessing that
God like
clearly
describes what Satan's move will be and
how it will be like we couldn't ask for
a better gift right let me yeah let's go
to the spirit of Prophecy let's watch
what she says now now that we understand
this watch this that now that we got the
foundation now that we got the
foundation right and there's more we're
goingon to go to we're gonna we haven't
even touched Daniel 11 yet but we will
notice what she says in the great
controversy through the two great errors
the immortality of the soul and Sunday
sacredness Satan will bring the people
under his deception
while the former lays a foundation of
spiritualism the latter creates a bond
of sympathy with Rome so I want you to
notice her use of the word spiritualism
right she says immortality of the soul
and Sunday sacredness the whole world
going to be brought under his deception
watch this the Protestants of the United
States will be foremost in stretching
their hands across the gulf to grasp the
hand of
spiritualism they will reach over the
abyss to clasp hands with the Roman
power and under this influence of the of
this threefold Union this country will
follow in the steps of Rome in trampling
on the rights of conscience so let me
mention something here man I it's
950 it's okay can we go a little later
that's why it's a series
well okay 10:30 whoa no we can't go to
10:30 all right because we have to
physically go to yeah
okay notice that it is only after the
uniting of
protestantism Catholicism and
spiritualism that this nation begins to
trample on the rights of
conscience it's not before let me say
this it has happened before this nation
has done that before
but not in connection with Rome not in
connection with with forcing worship the
way that Rome did back in during the
Dark Ages right so I'm not saying this
nation has never trapped upon the upon
conscience what I'm saying is within the
prophetic context right of what's going
to happen at the end of time so we're
looking for this then we're looking for
a coming
together of protestantism Catholicism
and
spiritualism we might say that this
coming together is what will bring the
whole world into deception in other
words we can't say this coming together
is the
healing of the deadly
wound when
protestantism grass hold of spiritualism
and Catholicism that is when the deadly
wound is healed because that is when the
image is set up that is when the whole
world wanders after the Beast and why do
they wonder they Wonder because of
spiritualism watch this y'all she's
speaking about this as something future
as though it has not happened yet now we
know that spiritualism has always been
here right you know communication with
the dead but she's talking about
something that is to happen in the
future that after that happens our
constitution is going to be done away
with every principle of the Constitution
is going to be done away with watch let
me keep reading reading from the same
place great controversy great
controversy page
588 she continues saying this as
spiritualism more closely imitates the
nominal Christianity of the day so pause
for a second because a lot of people out
there when they read spiritualism
they're thinking oh the new ages they're
thinking oh the the people who are
against God right she says here as
spiritualism more closely imitates the
nominal Christianity of the day it has
great power to deceive and and in snare
Satan himself was converted after the
modern of order thing of Mo after the
modern order of things now listen
carefully to this next sentence
y'all he will appear in the character of
an angel of Light is that what we just
saw in the
Bible she's equating spiritualism with
Satan appearing as an angel of Light let
me read it again as spiritualism more
closely imitates the nominal Christian
of the Christianity of the day it has
greater power to deceive it and snare
Satan himself is converted after the
modern order of things he will appear in
the character of an angel of Light she
is pointing here to Satan appearing as
Christ through the agency of
spiritualism Miracles will be wrought
the sick will be healed and many
undeniable wonders will be performed and
watch this as the spirits will profess
faith in the Bible and manifest respect
for the institution of the church their
work will be accepted as a manifestation
of divine power so at some point in the
future not a spirit but multiple
Spirits claiming to have risen from the
dead let me say this way it's almost
like there's going to come a point where
suddenly the veil between the seen and
the Unseen is removed it's going to be a
sudden event fire falling from the sky
and at that moment when Satan is
imitating the second coming of Christ
what do we know also happens at the
second coming of
Christ the dead are raised the dead are
raised y'all and that's the dead are
raised the dead are
raised someone is asking if we can
continue this this afternoon but this is
a series so next Sabbath will continue
well yeah yeah we're we will continue
I'm G to try to push for us to go a
little bit after like maybe 10 minutes
more yeah 10
15 20 20 no no no okay
so I'm not finished reading yet I'm
reading from great controversy I believe
this is chapter 36 let me mention
something else a lot of people get
confused about about this because they
look at the great controversy especially
chapters 36 to 40 as if it is written in
chronological order it is not written in
chronological order it is written on the
same Principle as the Book of Daniel
which is the principle of repeat and
enlarge so every chapter she's going
through the same thing but she's adding
more detail than the chapters before
right so people are thinking well the
Sunday law doesn't come until this or
Satan doesn't appear until chapter 4 no
no no here we are in chapter 36 and
she's talking about Satan appearing as
an angel of Light and in each chapter
she's going to build on this
theme okay so so watch this we're gonna
keep reading he will appear in the
character of an angel of Light right
many miracles will happen and these
Spirits spirits of the supposed dead
will will affirm now I want you to check
this out we're going to be in an
atmosphere where multiple Spirits not
not someone saying hey you know the dead
Spirit appeared to me like you know
that's happening hit and miss here and
there we're talking about a
global a glob thing happening watch this
she goes on the line of distinction
between professed Christians and the
ungodly is now hardly distinguishable
church members love what the world loves
and are ready to join with them and
Satan determines to unite them in one
body and thus strengthen his cause
listen to this by sweeping all into the
ranks of
spiritualism hopefully they're
understanding that clearly someone's
asking are they really raised from the
dead or does it appear to be raised
right right no they're not really raised
from the this these are counterfeit
Spirits this is
spiritualism this is Spirits
impersonating the dead that's what
spiritualism is and it's going to occur
on a massive scale in connection with
Satan himself as their head all of this
is going to make it appear that the
Millennium has begun Jesus is here and
look you atheist Jesus comes the dead
will be raised when Jesus comes the dead
will be raised and it's gonna be I mean
how do how do people know see watch this
in in the in in the in the Evangelical
version when Jesus comes he's coming
with the Saints from Heaven that's right
so it's going to be nothing yeah it's
going to be nothing for them to be like
oh look Paul and the apostles and
they're all back from heaven and they're
telling us that this is the New Order of
Things by the way watch this that's so
confusing it's not really confusing but
because in the Evangelical belief that
people go to heaven when they die so it
it's all a set being raised is
spiritualism has been building up for a
major event right so so when when Jesus
is now ruling on Earth guess what
atheists you were wrong guess what
Muslims you were wrong guess what
Buddhists yours is not the True Religion
guess what go down the guess what new
agers you were
wrong
and what choice do people have seeing is
believing here Jesus is y'all not only
Jesus but
spirits and they're all saying yep these
were my people they are pronouncing a
blessing on who the beast from the earth
and the Beast from the abyss I'm sorry
the beast from the earth and the Beast
from the sea they're pronouncing a
blessing upon apostate uh protestantism
and upon the papacy saying look these
were my Serv servants these are my
remnants and y'all were laughing at them
y'all were treating them in x y and z
now bow before they their feet I will
make the world to know that these were
my true disciples so I'm gonna play a
little I hate to say Devil's Advocate
which I I never do that but anyway but
um like hearing all of this clearly how
how Satan's deception and Miracle well
what will look like a miracle will um
try to counterfeit Jesus's real second
coming so
going back to where we are today and
people looking at today's events as
exactly uh this is preparing people this
is what you hear all the time or what
I've heard is that this is preparing
people to be deceived at that moment
they're being deceived now and this is
preparing them to be deceived then so
look y'all no I'm telling you it is not
V it is not climate control it is not
look at the pop latest and cyclical it
is not those things have no power to
convert the masses and all the different
religions to come on the same page and
worship the same God and so that's that
point right there is what people should
be Focus that's what people need to
understand right that it's it's when
Satan appears no question right that's
what's gonna happen right and listen
when Satan I hope my 14-year-old got
that when Satan is ruling on Earth you
you have a new form of government you no
longer have need for a constitution you
now have a
theocracy God himself is here ruling
Among Us you not have a theocracy and
that's why every principle of the
Constitution goes out the window it's
not one day the the the uh you know the
Republicans and Democrats decide you
know what let's all agree to throw the
Constitution out the window what they
will kill kill each other
first that's not going to happen under
normal circumstances not climate change
not covid nothing except a miracle and
what is that Miracle it is the miracle
of Satan appearing as Christ let me
continue reading on here and everyone
coming together coming together I'm I'm
reading from the same spot papists who
boast of Miracles as a certain sign of
the true church will be readily deceived
by this Wonder working power
she's speaking of it as something very
specific and Protestants having Cast
Away the shield of truth will also be
deluded it's yet future papists
Protestants and worldlings
alike will accept the form of godliness
without power and they will see in this
Union a grand movement for the
conversion of the world and the ushering
in of the long expected
Millennium wow
Protestants papists and worldlings alike
in other words beloved worldlings will
cease to be worldlings they will now
become quote unquote religious let me
read just a just a few more listen
continuing on same great controversy
page 588 and 589 I haven't skipped a a a
paragraph I'm reading straight
through through spiritualism Satan
appears as a benefactor of the race he
the disease of the diseases of the
people and professing to present a new
and more exalted system of religious
Faith but at the same time he works as a
destroyer it is when Satan appears as
Jesus that he's going to be healing but
at the same time causing destruction in
land sea and air and then saying yep
it's those people that refuse to keep my
Commandments that are messing up this
Millennium thing
I'm just going to read just one more
Satan has long been preparing for his
final efforts to deceive the world
effort to deceive the world the
foundation of his work was laid by the
Assurance given to Eve in Eden you shall
not surely die in the day you eat
thereof then your eyes shall be open and
you shall be as Gods knowing good and
evil little by little he has prepared
the way for his Masterpiece of descent
deception in the development of
spiritualism so not she's calling this
here his Mass he has many deceptions but
there is the Masterpiece of deception
and she says it will be through
spiritualism watch
this he has not yet reached the full
accomplishment of his designs but it
will be reached in The Last Remnant of
time says the
prophet I saw three unclean spirits like
frogs they are the spirits of devils
working miracles which go forth unto the
kings of the earth and to the whole
world to gather them to the battle of
the great day of God Almighty and then
she continu she continues with this
except those who are kept by the power
of God through faith in his word the
whole world will be swept into the ranks
of this
delusion the people are fast being
lulled to a fatal security only to be
awakened by the outpouring of the wrath
of God so she says here the whole world
world will be swept into the ranks of
this very specific and
particular
delusion specific particular it's a very
specific thing y'all and it doesn't
happen gradually right if it happens
gradually it's not an overwhelming
surprise yeah an overwhelming surprise
is something that catches all 10 virgins
off
guard wow listen y'all I have this is
not something new I've been preaching no
I've been preaching this for a very long
time go back and look at my my message
when America goes beast mode go back and
look at these messages four five6 some
of you like what happened to Pastor M he
changed what is he no no no no no no I
haven't changed I haven't changed I'm
still preaching
adventism I'm still trying to show look
at what the Bible says look what the
spirit of Prophecy says and this stuff I
was saying years and years and years ago
and because we are
so enamored with what signs next well
what we're now making signs where there
are none
right and this is leading to a whole lot
of confusion let me ask when is the last
time you heard a Minister preach about
the counterfeit appearing of Satan as
Christ when is the last time they
directed you to the verse in the Bible
that points out what elen white calls
the overmastering delusion the Final Act
and we're not preaching about it we're
not we're we are more
focused on the beast from the sea or the
beast from the Earth but nobody's
talking about the appearing of Christ
some people think oh they appear I mean
the appearing of Satan some people think
they appearing of Satan oh that happens
after probation close why will Satan
appear in an attempt to deceive the very
elect if there's still not an
opportunity for them to be deceived
right if it's the final test who's being
tested the wicked or the
righteous the wicked already doing what
they're doing it's the righteous that
are being tested it's the job situation
I bet you if you let me at them and try
to deceive them in any way that I can I
bet you that they'll bow the
KNE someone said even the elect will be
caught off guard first and foremost stay
grounded in the word of
God you guys
like I just read a straight I didn't
jump around Spirit of Prophecy I just
read straight through and that's just
one chapter y'all that's just one
chapter you think when you get caught
off guard like are you get surprised by
something because you're not looking or
you're not focused on the right area or
or thing that you're supposed to be
looking at so that you won't be thrown
off listen the reason why the 10 virgins
are all sleeping to this event is
because no there is no sign for when
Satan appears it's not like okay a year
from now all right this is the no there
is no sign so everybody is going to be
caught off guard but some will be
expecting it right God's Remnant should
be expecting it when Jesus said when you
therefore shall see the abomination of
desolation stand in the Holy place and
we'll get into that later we're not
going to be get into we'll get into that
later when we look at Daniel 11 when we
look at this this this this issue of the
King of the North coming against the
King of the South all right it's 10:08
I'm gonna do this maybe just recap the
most important things the the the key
things like if you could only if no like
okay might my last question right if a
person didn't get to hear or watch all
hour and three minutes and 30 seconds of
it and they were like tell me in one
minute the most important thing that I
need to take from this okay from today's
program The Deadly
wound was not
healed in 1929 with the ladan treaty all
the papacy became a you know um a a a
state
again was not healed in uh 1989 when
communism fell and
America and the papacy came together to
do that no those those are markers of oh
look things are happening like you know
the wound is healing it's in the process
of healing but the
persecution when that happens it is
because Satan himself has come to give
power to the beast power to to to these
entities that are claiming to serve God
but don't Satan himself will appear as
an angel of
Light Satan himself will be the will be
the entity that deceives the whole world
that is the miracle and he will right
and he'll return in a
fashion like you're expecting Jesus to
come I'm going to be preaching this in
my pre building on this in my sermon uh
at 11:30 but let me say this the be the
the three unclean spirits like frogs
that come out of the mouth of the Dragon
Beast and the false prophet that go for
to deceive the whole world the reason
why the Bible is using frogs is because
if you go back to the Exodus the
Miracles that were being performed by
Moses the frogs the miracle of the frogs
was the last miracle that the magicians
could
[Music]
counterfeit after the frogs they
couldn't counterfeit anymore so it was
the last counterfeit because Moses did
the frogs and they were like we're going
to counterfeit that they did the frogs
so the reason why frogs are being used
is because it's pointing to the fact
that this is the last counterfeit that
is going to take the whole world by
surprise and what is that last
counterfeit it is the same thing that
leads Michael to stand up in Daniel 121
and two and we're gonna pick up on that
next and we're gonna pick up on that in
the following
weeks in the North northeast corner of
Africa lies a country Fame for its
historic ruins incredible monuments Rich
culture giant pyramids and friendly
[Music]
people a country covered by the largest
desert on the planet the Sahara Desert
Egypt is arid sunny and Dusty a true
desert the N River the lifeblood of
Egypt is is the most important means for
supporting life in this harsh climate
this father of African Rivers is the
longest river in the world covering an
astounding
4,132 Mi it truly is the Wellspring the
sustainer of life in this historic Hot
Spot most life cannot survive in the
desert landscape of Egypt and yet Egypt
is known in history for being a thriving
superpower of antiquity the seed of all
other civilizations they were the master
Engineers well advanced in their time
they built their monuments as a
testament to their genius power and
pride they wanted to be remembered
forever just south of Cairo on a rocky
Plateau on the West Bank of the N River
sits the Pyramids of Giza the only
surviving wonder of the ancient world
there are three pyramids here each one
built to house the mummified bodies and
the physical Goods of three generations
of ferals father son and Grandson the
walls are inscribed with pictures and
texts of almost almost every subject
imaginable to this day scientists aren't
sure exactly how the Egyptians built
these ancient relics they stand as a
testament to their architectural skill
and genius near the Great Pyramid stands
one of the world's largest monuments the
Great Sphinx this colossal statue was
carved out of a single piece of
sandstone although it has deteriorated
over the centuries this ancient Relic is
still very much intact and it is
incredible sight to behold the city of
luxer sits Brad upon the banks of the N
River it is here that one-third of the
world's ancient monuments are found the
Valley of the Kings the Temple of luxer
the Temple of Carnac the Valley of the
Queens are just a few of the iconic
sites you can visit in this open air
museum temple ruins Royal burial grounds
ancient monuments are scattered across
this desert landscape there are some of
the oldest remaining monuments in the
world what's amazing about it is that
they built it in a time when they didn't
have electric or power tools they only
had pulley and manpower to accomplish
what they did with the technology that
they had is nothing short of amazing it
gives us a glimpse into the engineering
Genius of this ancient civilization
these structures have stood the test of
time but why was the ancient
civilization so successful and Powerful
how were they able to build these
incredible monuments instead of Simply
laboring for survival in this harsh
desert land that which all these
monuments have in common is that they
were built near the water the great n
river is the lifeline of ancient Egypt
being used as a source of food water
transportation and irrigation for crops
without the Nile life would not have
been possible in this region of the
world without the Nile they would never
have the time or ability to erect these
massive monuments their life and their
legacy was built on the banks of the
Nile the lesson is simple but profound
in its simp licity if you want to
survive and thrive in life like the
ancient Egyptians you need to align your
life with an environment most favorable
for Success if you want the Temple of
your legacy and the Monument of your
influence to remain long after you're
gone you need to build by the river the
place most favorable for growth and
prosperity it's all about location now
you may not have had the chance to
choose the literal location of where you
live but there are many other areas in
life where we do have the power to
decide like who we surround oursel with
what we put in front of our eyes the
voices we choose to listen to what we
consume physically mentally and
spiritually the friends and influencers
we choose to follow these are the things
that we can control we must stop setting
up our tents in the desert of lifeless
thinking we need to avoid mentally
habituating in the sifting sinking sand
of selfish worldly philosophy that's
constantly changing with the blowing
Winds of empty trends of vain importance
a house cannot stand when its foundation
is sinking sand like the ancient
Egyptians if we want our house to stand
and the legacy of our monuments to last
for Time and Eternity we must build our
lives and our Legacy near the river for
it is a Life and Legacy built by the
river that will impact future
Generations we must set Our Roots down
by the river we must feed upon the
life-giving Water of positive thinking
gratitude in times of difficulty delayed
gratification self- sacrifice faith hope
and a Heavenly love that is demonstrated
in service to others these are the
characteristics that will Outlast the
elements for the god that came to this
ancient land many generations ago gave
to all of us the promise that when we
walk not in the Council of the ungodly
when we stand not in the path of Sinners
when we avoid sitting in the seat of the
scornful but instead Delight in his ways
and meditate upon his righteousness day
and night that as a result we shall be
like a tree planted by the rivers of
water whose leaves are always green and
fruit is always tasty and whatever we do
will
prosper and so I invite you today to
come out of the desert ignore the
deceptive Mirage that will leave you
unsatisfied Come to the River of Life
now you may not be able to come to the
Nile like we've done so today but there
is another River that is within the
reach of a there is a river whose stream
shall make glad the city of God the holy
place of the Tabernacles of the most
high the unmovable Monument of your life
is built by the river of God's grace and
the water of his Divine favor all can
come all can drink you need not be a
pharaoh to have a monument named after
you all you must do is come by faith to
the King of Kings from whose Throne
flows the River of Life and there he
will give you everything that you need
to overcome the challenges and thrive in
the desert of this world so go where the
water flows it is the best place to sew
and the place most favorable to grow and
when your fruit begins to show then all
will know and they too will be drawn to
where the water flows
[Music]
we hope you've been blessed and inspired
by this new reflections of Hope episode
this episode is one of many that's been
produced all over the world if you
haven't done so yet please give our
video a like share it with your friends
and please follow us on Instagram
Facebook and YouTube if you'd like to
see more inspiring episodes and get
access to much more uplifting content
please go now to
patreon.com revelation of Hope and sign
up to be a member of our patreon page
your monthly support will not only give
you Early Access to many more inspiring
videos but it will also enable us to
continue to produce more of these
cinematic object lessons from nature our
goal is to produce and release these
episodes much more frequently so please
prayerfully consider partnering with us
so that we may continue to share the
hope of Jesus all over the world thank
you so much for your support Aloha and
marinata
[Music]
[Applause]
he
[Music]
and welcome welcome welcome back here to
living Mana Church you have now entered
into our divine worship service and
we're so thankful to have you hanging
there with us from Sabbath school once
again if you did not get nuggets from
Back to Basics part one that broadcast
that was aired originally uh during the
pandemic you'll see some of with the
timeline but the information is still so
relevant it has sparked such a
conversation with us even on the back
end with the tech team and with Pastor
Lami and so we are on fire and so
grateful for these messages if at any
time you want to see the re broadcast
please make sure you come back to our uh
YouTube channel here U on living Mana
church and be able to take that word in
even deeper and please make sure you
grab the link and share it because also
that digital disciple you guys are are
flexing I'm telling you're flexing and
it is reflecting in the numers increase
of followers here on the Liv Man YouTube
channel right now uh we've got to uh
take the opportunity to say welcome to
everybody here I'm going to look here in
our restream and say hello to some of
our members Kashif Williams Happy
Sabbath to you Ayana wants again hello
sister shaen God bless you Happy Sabbath
to you and so many others Clint eyes I
see you in the building as well and for
those of you who are just joining with
us live and don't know who I am I'm
Patrice delisser I am the secretary here
for living Mana church and I'm sitting
in for my dear sister at tante um as you
know they are mourning the loss of her
brother-in-law the sweet Shawn Meyers
and uh we asking continued prayers for
them and we'll be sharing just
momentarily how you can show your
support and sending cards or just
thoughts but more importantly they're so
appreciative of your prayers that
continue to hold and sustain them uh we
asking your continued blessing and
prayers to uphold Sean's lovely wife
Veronica and their children um and uh
just you know our hearts continue to be
poured out to them as they're preparing
for the actual service that will be
taking place and you'll get more
information on that uh right now I'm
going to invite our co-pastor here at
Living Mana Church assistant pastor Lami
Richardson will be joining me right now
because we're about to do a live
transfer of membership Pastor Lami how
are you I'm a little under the weather
but I'm blessed to be with my church
family and like I said Patrice you ain't
lying the discussions we have behind the
scenes is really the real conversations
of heart so if you guys haven't been
listening to these Sabbath schools
lessons it is very uh great information
I think uh our our understanding of
Bible prophecy and just scriptures um
has been such a huge blessing so I
thoroughly enjoy our conversations
behind the scenes that people don't get
to hear but happy Sab from everyone I'm
part of the living Mana church family
and I'm part of ofy Richardson as the
young adult and associate pastor welcome
again thank you so much and so we've got
uh some business of order that we're
going to touch first and then we're
going to talk to you uh Pastor Lami
about a program that is going to be
premiering uh in February so we're going
to give an opportunity to talk about
that a little bit as well so right now
we've got some housekeeping to do
transfer of membership and this is a one
because they're transferring from living
Mana Church to uh floral the floral SDA
church and so right now we have a second
reading of transfer membership out from
living Mana church and the name is Sarah
merer she is transferring to from living
Mana Church to the floral Crest 7 the
Adventist Church right now U we're
passing the mic to past Lami to go ahead
and do the proper uh procedure to make
that trans for her possible but Sarah
please know and I know you do know
you're always free to come back here
you're always part of living man church
family and we're so thankful you're able
to find a physical home that you feel
connected to as well but you're always
welcome here so we're going to miss you
but you're still part of our family so
I'm going to turn over to pastor wamy
this time all right so we'll start with
the second reading for the transfer of
Sarah Mercers to Flora Crest SDA Church
um if I can get a motion um if I can get
a motion for the transfer of
Sarah do we have a
motion yeah we have a little bit of laty
just for a couple seconds okay uh
brother Terry has put in the
motion all right motion has been granted
and do is there any
questions any questions in the
chats no questions if not we will then
in favor of the transfer you can please
put a one in the chat these are for the
members of the living man and SDA church
if you can put one in the chat in
favor we have we have that all right
great those
oppos there's no opposition and it's
been voted and so Sarah part of the
Living
Church all right Sarah as a part of the
living man of church even though you're
not an official member you're always a
part of the family and we thank you so
much for being a part of this journey
with us and blessings on your new
Endeavor and so anybody else who's
interested in joining and being part of
the living Mana church you can uh
contact Patrice and we can uh work on
how we can make that happen for you guys
if you guys are interested in joining
the the Liv the living Mana
family awesome awesome so right now I
wanted to take the opportunity because
this would have been a stagnant
announcement I'm going to make um on the
screen but what a perfect opportunity
while he is yet here with us live uh
past Mami has a brand new
program excited this program for
Millennials and genz but I'm sure it's
open to everybody and Pastor I want to
give you the opportunity to really kind
of unpack that a little bit and share it
and encourage everybody to uh when it's
going to be on and um what's the program
is about and how we can support
I don't hear past
lwami let's see if we can get him back
in the
room let's see if we can get past Lami
back in the building I see the
slide okay all right can you hear me now
can you hear me now ah we can hear you
yes okay we can take the the slide down
thank you so much all right so as a part
of um uh as as being a part of the
living matter family they was an
emphasis on really trying to Target our
young adults our Millennials and gen Z
audience um that was specifically not
just wanting to learn about Bible
prophecy but about the real topics that
affects our everyday lives and Patrice
you kind of got an example of that uh
this afternoon this this morning as we
was talking about the relevancy of you
know how people are struggling
financially people are dealing with real
life issues and I I realized that the
more I have engaged with young adults
and engage with uh of uh Millennials and
Jers there there there doesn't seem to
be a safe place where people can just be
open transparent about their struggles
about their questions about their doubts
about their insecurities about whatever
it is that is pertaining into their
heart and giving practical uh Biblical
advice to how to navigate through these
real life issues as someone who
navigated through mental health and
dealt with anxiety dealt with depression
of trying to navigate of what means like
to be an adult listen I just celebrated
my 40th birthday and I feel like I'm 25
I feel like I have no understanding of
how life works because it keeps on
moving and these are real life things
that we struggle with and so as much as
the 11 o'clock hour and Sabbath services
and mental health all these other
programs have been such a blessing for
me and for the audience at large we
wanted to kind of create a very specific
program for our young adult community to
ask questions to hear interviews from
other walks of life and the experiences
just a few weeks ago I had my friend
wifredo talk about grief that's
something that we usually don't talk
about and how we process grief people
process grief in different ways but from
that interview I learned man he took his
grief and was able to pour into an art
that God has blessed him to have and is
able to bless more people in that in in
in in the sphere of his impact through
music and so our Thursday night programs
will be uh will be kind of twofold where
every other week or at least once a
month we'll have a special guest coming
in to talk about a very relevant topic
whether it be about finances whether it
be about mental health or any other
topic that that is uh relevant uh during
that time but also uh conversations and
and studies on how we can better
understand how to navigate as a
Millennial Christian in this day and age
and one thing I noticed and I've learned
is that God is Not Afraid of our
questions he's not afraid of our
struggles he's not afraid of the things
that we experience right people have
questions you know is is smoking bad you
know is is is it okay for me to get a
tattoo is it you know these are real
questions that I think sometimes when we
ask people's like well we got to pray
that they're not drifting away from the
Lord when in reality they're just
inquiring questions because these are
things that people may present to them
and they may not have an answered to and
so that's what the safe place is about
where you can come in you can talk we
can ask questions and we can learn from
each other without feeling oh I can't
ask that question because somebody's
going to judge me or they're going to
excommunicate me from the church or
anything like that this is a program
that is gear geared specifically towards
gen Z and Millennials to talk about
relevant topics that are dear to our
hearts and I'll tell you this once we
create those safe places once we become
more vulnerable more honest of where
we're at and we can get real answers
right without well I said it and God
said it that's you know that's the end
of it I think we will be able to have
far more impact and Outreach especially
to the everyday people that we come in
contact with because the reality is once
we leave out of this bubble we have to
deal with life and how we navigate as
Christians and and understand how the
gospel Works in our everyday life
shouldn't be a theory it should be
something that is learned and is
practically lived out and so that's what
the safe place is about and we'll be
meeting Thursday nights at 8:00 pm uh
starting in February uh date to be
determined as you know as um since you
know everything that's been happening um
with the Living manate Church and with
Pastor Myers so we had to put we have
put a pause on the program for this
month but we'll resume in February so
keep a lookout if you haven't joined the
the mighty networks please join the
mighty networks join the uh safe place
and the struggle is real um group chat
and if you have any questions is there
that we are able to answer it and so I'm
excited about this new program um and
I'm excited about the people we're about
to interview and the topics we're going
to talk about and uh one of the things
that we're going to talk about um in our
first session is going to be how do we
deal with not only grief but how do we
deal with addictions and it's crazy to
understand that addictions is not just
well I'm addicted to pornography or I'm
addicted to drinking there are actually
other addictions that we deal with that
we may not know it's an addiction but
it's actually something that we need to
resolve and understand as to why we
gravitate to these things and so these
are these are just an example of some of
the topics excuse me that we're going to
talk about um on the safe place on
Thursday nights for our young adult
program I'm excit I'm excited about I'm
excited about not because you're doing
it but I'm excited because the things I
love about living Mana church and
particular the vision that God gave
Pastor Myers uh through this Vision was
to open up channels and opportunity to
reach all the different uh Generations
within the congregation worldwide and
not just from the ones who are members
here but those who watch on a regular
basis and um not being afraid and I like
the ttle of the fact the safe place to
be open to hear and I and I'm going to
admonish because he probably won't do it
but I will um be open to hear and don't
judge just open to hear because if you
don't hear what's on the heart of the
generations that were before you and
this will give is an indication of what
the next Generations even after gen Z is
going to be having to focus on and so we
want to create those spaces of community
of Love of understanding but also
in a way that's point is going to point
them in a loving way what did Jesus have
to say how did Jesus navigate through
this time if Jesus would did not come
when he did and if Jesus were to come
here in 2025 where would we find
Jesus we he'd find him talking he would
find him in in the area in which I live
it would be a kinsington area where the
drug addicts are and where the needles
are are literally on the ground this is
where you would find Jesus and this is
the culture that we wanted really help
and really give an opportunity to say
this church is open for jenes for
Millennials for everybody you are
welcome here and you're part of the
family and everyone here is a valued
Soul so um thank you so much Pastor Lamy
for allowing the Lord to use you to give
you the vision for it thank you Pastor
Myers for being open for the program um
because I do know all the pieces of the
puzzles put together makes a global
family so thank you so much and um thank
you so much all right so take care so
everybody here at Living Min church we
are going to be going into our
announcements but I really want to take
this opportunity and a great way for
pastor Lami himself to explain what the
program is about and I know you got it
and I know you're going to support and I
also want to make sure you share that
link when the program comes on so please
make sure you do all right so let's get
into our church announcements and we've
got so much listen here listen here
listen here you know I always get
excited about this because you guys know
who you're part of the text family you
have been getting these alerts in real
time as we started I got an alert on my
phone and every time I come on here I'm
going to let you know I really did get
an alert so our text our text team is
really on fire getting the notifications
out to you on a real time basis even
ahead of time so you can get prepared to
grab your lunch or sit down or whatever
the programs are coming up through the
week so um please if you have not signed
up up please make sure you do at LM text
8552741386
1207 4107 and if you're on your laptop
you can grab your phone take a
screenshot of the uh scan the QR code
and it'll immediately take you there to
sign up there and this is great for the
United States but those of you who know
um you're not a part of it because
you're outside we did not leave you
behind because we got the money networks
M networks is on fire I promise you even
if you're if you have not signed up can
I take a moment encourage you to sign up
to myy
networks I just gave you a moment you
should have signed up be a part of
Mighty networks because you really do
have an opportunity to engage with your
other brothers and sisters they've got
the prayer wall they've got women
Ministries they've got all kinds of
things they're posting prayers they're
posting songs they're and you know
sending messages to each other just
encouraging one another and it is such
an active Community platform for
everybody around the world so and every
I've tell to you every now and then
Pastor miles will pop up on there and do
a quick video or quick live on there and
so we are excited about that so please
make sure you sign up for myy networks
so LM Mo
kids was happening in real time when
Sabbath school started Shout shout out
to living Mana kids teachers who were
already on duty they showed up at 11:30
Central Standard Time and we're already
working with your kids when our service
went live so shout out to you to the
team and the please if you have not
signed your children up to be a part of
it please make sure you do that they are
wonderfully teaching your your
children's scriptures and text and
encouraging Community right there on
that platform so if you have not signed
up your children or your if you're
grandparent if you're a care keeper and
you know if you're a babysitter and
you're babysitting a child at the time
that this is happening hey please ask
the parents can I sign your kids for
this and it's so wonderful and engaging
so please make sure you text kids to
8552741386
okay we just had a transfer of reading
out from living Mana Church Sarah we're
sorry to see you go but we totally
understand um but if you want to become
a member of living Mana church you can
send me an email personally to Patrice
Liv mana. live and if it's by profession
of faith that you've been baptized in
another congregation and you want to
become a member of living Mana church or
if you have not been a member of any
church and you want Bible study and
baptism you can also send me that
information that I want to become I want
to do Bible studies and be baptized in
the lanic church and you can also send
me that information as well and if
you're already member of another
Adventist Church and you want to just do
a transfer of membership from that
church to this one the same way Sarah
did it from this church to the uh the
church at the floral the floral SDA
church you can do that as well so just
make sure you send me that information
and we will process that at due
diligence we are really diligent about
our membership trans here at Living Mana
Church um our Virtual Office visits and
so if you those of you who are seeking
that um please still feel free to send
me the information uh we will put you on
the list and right now it is paused but
I you're in the queue for Virtual Office
hours so when Pastor Myers returns back
to start the virtual hours he will begin
to contact you and make sure uh you put
in the time zones the best days and
times for him to reach you and that way
he'll be able to to connect with you
because he is in the Central Standard
time zone and so you will coordinate
that with you but he will be in touch
with you directly but for those of you
who'd like to set up and be in queue for
a virtual office visit with Pastor Myers
please make sure you see the email there
to send me an email request for that so
our prayer requests um those of you
right now have been putting your prayers
in the chat since Sabbath School began
and I encourage you even right now put
those prayers in the comments our prayer
warriors are are Skyping them and
sniping them out as you're putting them
up there and definitely um we want to
make sure those of you who got your
answer prayers make sure you just also
respond hey my prayers were answered so
for all your prayer requests please make
sure you put them in the comments live
or you can send an email to pray p r y
Liv mana. Church um on the mighty
networks you can also put there's a
prayer wall you can put your prayer
request there as well and you can also
text pray for f r to
4107 um to now be a part and subscribe
to our living man YouTube channel which
is growing I want to give you guys a
shout out because last week we're at
5,600 this as of today we're at 5,000
sorry
5,960 we are now
5,970 we just need 30 more people and we
will be at the 6,000 Mark so for those
of you who are watching on the power of
the Lamb Channel please make sure you
sweep right over and click that follow
for living Mana church or just share the
link period if you're on living Mana
right now share the link encourage
everyone to come and just follow the
YouTube uh channel here at Living mana
and follow us on all of our social media
and you'll see it right there at living
manor we're on Tik Tok we're on
Instagram we are uh Facebook we are
everywhere to make sure that the Three
Angels message Goes Forth so please make
sure uh you encourage others to follow
us here on all of our social media
platforms okay so let's take a breath
um as I mentioned earlier the services
we're going to give the information and
put that slide up right now for Shawn
Meyers uh the dear brother of Pastor
Ivor Meyers brother-in-law's sister
tante and the son of Mr Mrs Myers and
brothers and husband of Veronica
okay so here we are the information is
there on the screen for you the
celebration of life will be taking place
this Thursday on January the 30th the
service time will be 9:30 a.m. eastern
time and the repass will be 12: to 3 um
the services will be taking place at the
southern Asian SDA Church
20001 2001 East Randolph Road in Silver
Spring Maryland and for those of you who
would like to uh continue to send cards
of condolences to the Myers family you
can send that to the living manner
Church P box 428 attention Myers family
Owens Crossroads Alabama ZIP code
35763 so I will keep this there
momentarily and those of you who on your
laptops if you want to scan the QR codes
for either for the RSVP for the
celebration of life or the scan the code
right now where they cons send cards you
can do that I'm going give you a pause a
moment here and let you do that that um
before we move on to the next
announcement so thank you guys so much
for for the love and prayers of the for
the Myers family they as I mentioned
earlier they really do feel it and that
has come directly from Sister Myers and
and Pastor Myers um so continue to hold
them up this week um and so thank you
guys we really appreciate it all right
so now we have um um information about
our
convocation our convocation will be Tak
place but our convocation has a date
change so you'll see here it says May
1st through the 4th of this year um we
actually are the date has been moved and
I think the slide should be up here
momentarily um the date change has been
moved to October 31st through November
the 2nd of this year it's in the same
location so um those of you who are
saying I was trying to make it to may
but I wasn't sure but now you be you've
got that little you got a little more
grace and so they've pushed it back to
October 31st through November the 2nd
and it will still be at the same
location in Orlando Florida uh still at
the wendum so everything is the same so
you have an opportunity to still go
ahead and register get those planes and
I know now we're going to be changing
things in terms of and and this this
probably works out even well too because
the changes as far as um just the
immigration how you're going to be
flying into the country and out the
country so please this more time for you
to get that valuable information set up
so you can go ahead and make sure you're
here for October 31st through the 2nd
for the Breath of Life convocation um
that will be done by Pastor Ivor Meers
that is living man Church convocation
and we cannot wait we are still just as
anxious to be able to see you guys in
person so excited about that so we have
an announcement here about our Bible
workers um so for our Bible workers
we'll put that slide up as well if you
would like to become a Bible worker uh
please make sure you send it to Bible
worker at Living mana. Church um we are
so grateful
for um our Bible worker leader who is on
fire doing the Bible studies but you
know the scripture says you know it we
have we're in need of more workers and
the field is white and so we definitely
need more workers so you will receive
Bible worker training and be able to
share the Gospel of Jesus Christ and
three Angels message right there so for
our Bible workers you'll see that on the
screen as well so right now yeah we
talked about that already we talked
about the breath breath of life there it
is there's a slide right there in CMI
Florida which is just right side of
Orlando um October 31st through November
the 2nd uh for the Breath of Life
convocation so you will have that
information right there on on the screen
for you okay our next announcement is
our women's ministry our Min women's
ministry is up and running we are
excited about that um the women's
ministry Almighty Network led by our
beloved sister Joan Stephen she is
amazing uh and they're saying hey please
join us for enriching studies heartfelt
devotionals and powerful prayers stay
connected and grow together in faith
with our supportive community
and please make sure if you especially
if you're woman in need of community and
you don't have like maybe other
believers that you connect with and you
don't you don't have to necessarily be a
member of Li Mana church this is for all
women calling all women to be a part of
this beautiful Liv uh women's ministry
program here and you can sign up and be
a part of it on the mighty networks our
next announcement is our mental health
Mondays will be returning that's right
sister tante and Dr white will be back
with us live February the 4th here on
the living mattera YouTube channel and
uh you know we have been missing her and
we understand um that they have
definitely have needed time and so she's
anxious and looking forward as well as
Dr M Carter W of coming back and sharing
some valuable information and health
nuggets with you so please make sure you
turn on your notifications here on the
YouTube channel get those notifications
when it go live and once again when you
sign up for the Tex alerts you already
get that alert letting you know the
broadcast is coming back on live so
we're excited about that and please make
sure if you have enjoyed any of the
programs um they're rebroadcasting as
well on Mondays so do not still miss out
on any helpful and valuable information
from mental health Mondays and we've
already talked about safe place we going
to put that slide back up again here on
safe place that new program that be done
by Pastor associate pastor Lami
Richardson and he just gave an outline
and description of what the program is
about for millennials and Jers please
make sure you keep those notifications
on and we will let you know exactly when
it begins in February so we are excited
about that and please make sure when you
see it come on you share that live share
the link share it right now and even
prepare right now to share the slide if
you got take a screenshot of the slide
and send it to young young person uh
please make sure you do that as well um
right now we are now going
into our living Mana glob Channel we're
so thrilled about the fact that we are
able to have the actual messages that
Pastor Myers and even our guest speakers
are sharing and they are being
translated into countless languages and
we are so grateful for that even the
slides they present are done in their
actual language so everything from
Italian to Korean to Spanish uh it the
list goes on and on and still growing so
we are thankful for that um Avenue to be
able to get the Three Angels message out
through there and so make sure uh you
have individuals that you know in your
life that speak any of those languages
and you want to share them and you don't
know how to do that just copy the link
share the channel and let the Holy
Spirit do what only the Holy Spirit does
and so we're excited about that all
right so right now we're going into our
corporate worship and our corporate
worship is into our giving and right now
we want to take an opportunity to remind
you how you can uh remit your tithe and
offering here at Livy man Church our
first way of doing so is through the
adventistgiving.org
platform and when you sign up there and
you can select the M living man Church
you'll see a virtual envelope that pops
up and the tithe is that 10% of your
income that is designated as a tithe and
our local budget which is what God has
put in your heart as a sacrificial
giving and your generosity has truly
been felt here as as supporting the
local church we have been able to help
so many people uh as for you know in
your place to so if you can't do it
yourself we have definitely been
receiving just requests for help with
school education some health challenges
and it has been a blessing to be able to
Steward your giving and dollars well to
the glory of God and so we want to ask
you right now that if you could
please earmark uh what is tithe for the
local church we want to make sure that
you do know there on those blank areas
if you want to give just particularly to
education um that you let let us know
exactly where that want you where you
want that place and we are so thankful
to make sure that those dollars go where
you like it to go the other way of doing
so is through our mail system yes we are
still using the mail and we'll continue
to do so because a lot of people can't
use the uh online platform so you can
send your uh your check to make it out
to living Mana church and make it out to
PO Box 428 Owens Crossroads Alabama ZIP
code 35763 and please make sure send a
note or a little letter or card
outlining exactly what is tithe what is
offering or if it's a special gift for a
particular uh Ministry program please
make sure you denote that as well on the
note so we can make sure your money is
applied to where you would like to be
applied and I can testify that your
dollars truly are honored here in
integrity and so we are so excited about
that so right now want to take an
opportunity to pray for our offering
giving um right and also look forward to
the fact that you are putting your
prayer requests in the chat as we as I'm
speaking also you know Pastor Myers does
not leave us without fresh bread and our
own brother Terry soul will be bringing
fresh bread to us he is the director of
our prayer team here at liby Mana church
and it is an honor truly for us to serve
with him so at this time I'm going to
lift up the offering in prayer heavenly
father thank you so much for the
blessing and the opportunity to connect
with our brothers and sisters around the
world thank you for the giving that is
even in progress and it's already
started before we even came on live and
we thank you and ask your blessing upon
those who were able to give and those
who would like to give um we're asking
that you will bless them with with the
resources uh to be able to participate
in this part of this worship service as
well um we thank you so much for their
constant contributions we thank you for
their diligence and honoring you in
their sacrificial giving but we also
thank you for their heart Lord that
where they they can go physically they
know that their financial resources are
going before them to reach the world for
your kingdom thank you so much for this
opportunity to pray in Jesus name amen
God bless you all and we'll see you soon
[Music]
oh
I'll never be more loved than I am right
now wasn't holding you up so there is
nothing I can do to let you
down it doesn't take a
trophy to make you
proud I'll never be more loved than I am
right
now
oh going through a storm but I won't go
down I hear your voice carried in the
Rhythm Of The Wind call me out
you would cross an ocean so I wouldn't
drown you've never been closer than you
are right now
Gyra
gy you are
enough oh
[Applause]
J you I
know and I will be content
in every
circumstance you are
G you are
enough I don't want to
forget how I feel right now on the
Mountaintop I can see so clear what it's
all
about so stay by my side when the Sun
goes down
own don't want to forget how I feel
right now
Gyra
JRA you are
enough oh
J you are
enough and I will be
content in every
circumstance you are Gus
you are in
love I'm already
loved I'm already
chosen I know who I
am I know what you're
spoken I'm already
loved more than I could
imagine and that is enough
[Applause]
I'm already
Lov I'm already
chosen I know who I am yeah I know what
you
spoken I'm already
love more than I could
imagine and that is
enough that is enough what is test is
better than
anything that is enough I don't need
money or material
things that is
enough that is
enough Lord you are enough
enough you are
enough you are enough
jeh you are else should die you
are
G you are
enough
J you are
enough and I will be
content in every
circumstance that you are a g
you are in
[Music]
love here at Living Mana we bear each
other's burdens when you need support or
prayer when you're feeling
discouraged or alone or
anxious you don't have to face life
struggles alone
[Music]
let us come boldly unto the throne of
grace that we may obtain mercy and find
Grace to help in our time of
need the Lord is close to the
Brokenhearted and saves those who are
crushed in spirit
[Music]
greetings Saints of the most high God
happy Sabbath and welcome to another uh
segment of living mana's prayer and
praise time as always I am here with my
lovely brother
amra and um we are happy and excited to
be able to serve the Lord and serve you
his people in this awesome com capacity
here okay so brother Terry's got to
untie his tongue
today and get it all together you know
what want to just say we love your
living man of family sending shout outs
to everybody that we you know we always
talk good B you and stuff but I see some
people in the chat and saying hi and we
want to say hey to y'all too brother
Robert love you um brother brother Clint
always exciting to see you my brother
God bless you God bless you Sister uh
sister Regina you and sister estralita
I'm not gonna steal ammer th Thunder but
y'all about to make a brother jump out
of this chair and Shout with that live
praise report that just came we'll talk
about that in a minute hello
Harriet yes sister Harriet we're praying
too sister sister Harriet has an issue
we've been praying about that we'll
continue to pray during intercessory
prayer Our beloved brother Danny and
sister Jackie are going to come and lead
us in accessory prayer today and we will
be remembering you and the issues you
dealing with after the fires down in Los
Angeles we know the Lord is our healer
so love you so much sister Ayana my
waret sister love you so much there and
last week I was doing the the uh roll
call for Trinidad and Tobago and my
lovely bride just interrupted that so
maybe next time we'll do Joanne Val love
y'all all everybody down there and and
beautiful hello Robin Robin Jerry
my sister Jerry and thank you for
serving back up for me today and sitting
in for me at the altar so y'all come on
after the service today to altar live
and let's have some fellowship and have
a good time Bond get to know one another
share our what we are learning what the
Lord's saying to us sister Jerry will be
doing uh the Afterglow today so thank
God for her and uh again hello artel
thank you
brother artel amen and and then you know
what to today there was a great shout
out for lmos a kids so sister Tanya
sister Jerry sister JoJo Lawrence and PJ
love y'all y'all doing an amazing job
keep up the good work keep up the good
work over there
amen so there was one other thing you
didn't have a roll call today pretty
much did didn't we I mean oh I guess
look at the top of the Roll Call I want
to shout out my beloved brother
my pastor my family and friends Pastor
Meyer and first lady sister at tante we
love y'all thank God so much for y'all
May the joy of the Lord just flood your
heart to overflowing May the peace of
God that just don't even make no sense
just bless you and touch your lives in
every way we all love you we're sending
shout outs to you right now from
everybody viewing everybody watching
Everybody in the chat we're sending our
love and our prayers to you and uh we
just continually thank God for you amen
uh we were watching that Back to Basics
this morning let me tell you never ever
ever gets old and it's becoming more and
more R relevant as as as the days go by
so uh man we can't get enough of that
and I don't know if we're gonna probably
go through the whole series or not it's
doing Sabbath school but that's some
powerful stuff and so want to encourage
everybody go back go back and watch uh
the entire series and uh if if there's
questions you have you can always back
it up and go again so that's some good
stuff sure
I see you in the chat we'll be praying
for you and we love you very much amen
sister Charlotte is an absolute Soldier
she is in a different rehab after a
fall Lord have mercy I mean Sister
Charlotte I really admire you because I
mean you're a soldier a war yet and keep
right on pressing on so beautiful thank
you so much sister Christina love you
love you so much sister Nicole love you
sister anetta we wanted to share with
you and let you know that we do we love
and appreciate you and what you do and
so every member of the living Mana
family I don't care what it is you do
here you know the Lord's got a word
today I'm not going to get ahead of
myself but I believe the Lord has
something to say to every one of us to
bless our heart and so pray for me today
that God will will help us to just land
this word home in such a way that we'll
know that we know that we know we've
heard from heaven today amen Jesus name
so what what you got beloved okay well
before I get into the praise reports
just a reminder that if you have a
prayer request or a praise report that
you would like to submit to the prayer
team please send an email to pray Living
mana. Church if you would like to join
our prayer team which is so Lively in an
amazing Community you would not regret
it or you would like to join a special
ops prayer team under the prayer team
window you would also send an email to
the same address at pray Living mana.
Church if you have a special request for
special ops team for yourself or a loved
one please submit your request to spec
ops that's SP Ops at Living mana. Church
if you would like to join the women's
ministry on Mighty networks and they are
very Lively and engaging please send an
email to women Living mana. Church
that's
Wen Living mana. Church and finally if
you would like to join the Men's
Ministry and they deal with a lot of
topics and a lot of things that men go
through that us women just couldn't
understand please send an email to seven
loaves that's SE n l o a VES Living
mana.
Church now going into the praise reports
the first one coming from Sandy
Peterson it has been way too long for me
to send an update on Dakota I pray that
you all are well and that your prayer
team's prayers have been being have been
being answered I love the work you do my
husband and I were fortunate to spend
the Christmas holiday with Dakota his
little family and our good friends his
parents I'm happy to report that Dakota
remains stable and continues to take his
chemo
medication a pill daily for a week at a
time then has two weeks off it causes
him to have fatigue and nausea but is
tolerating but he is tolerating
everything I'm happy to report that our
prayers for for Dakota are being
answered I'm not sure when his next MRI
will be but when those results come I
will update the prayer team our God is
so good and I Just Praise Him for giving
Dakota more time with his family please
pray that Dakota turns his heart and
Life to God amen
amen from Shaunie this is the original
prayer please pray for my sister's
friend's young granddaughter Ayana she
broke her jaw playing sports yesterday
and will be in surgery within the next
hour
please pray the surgery they are
performing will be successful and that
she won't have to have her jaw wired for
six weeks thank you and the praise my
friend just sent me an update praise God
for his mercy and loving care wonderful
news Ayan is out of surgery with
titanium plates and screws in place she
doesn't have to have her Jaws wired shut
Hallelujah now it's just healing time
but they don't answer anticipate any
problems thank you all so much for the
prayers love you
all and we caught this praise report in
the chat this is from Regina B about her
Mom Estella white praise report my
mother's doctor called today revealing
that her brain MRI results are fine
praise God hallelujah yeah amen praise
God Amen what a blessing absolutely and
she actually said my doctor just called
so that that just happened that's a
fresh praise praise the Lord amen fresh
praise this is a little different I'm
excited to read this one but this is a
little little different so this one
comes from James IES and he says this is
a praise of A Sort written by Clint IES
led by the spirit it's called scars and
calluses
love love is something I've learn I'm
learning more and more about I mean real
real standing for righteous Eternal
anointing love this love is new only to
my eyes meaning I was blind to it before
but it was always there he was always
there like a lot of people I was blind
since birth spiritually speaking of
course I was raised to be tough building
calluses ignoring scars
through this I was Burying my headache
along with my heart the journey has been
long but there is still some tread left
on these tires the Lord has shown me
that the heartache I feel is not to be
buried or ran from rather early rains
for latter growth I've considered how
the world once was with the Mists coming
up from the earth in this I see the
tears that rise out of me and soften
this hard ground soften these callous
I've built over my heart you see the
calluses are works of men the scars are
the love of God I hope you see the
difference the Lord obtained his scars
from diving head first into our thorny
Sin Sin filled Graves and pulling us out
that is love a scar be it physical
emotional spiritual all for the
cultivation of God's Garden a healed
reminder albe it that fully healed lest
you forget the Lord has shown me to
remember all the heartache and the loss
I feel and let those rainwaters
cultivate in me a tree of life Saints
this tree is growing you see I love
fiercely I hold on to people fiercely
but all of my strength and the rest of
the worlds isn't enough to hold on to
those we lost so he that loves more
fiercely than I ever could told me to
hold on to him and his scarred hands for
his grip is true his love is real and he
spelled that re a l which again stands
for righteous Eternal anointing love
amen amen that was beautiful it it is
beautiful thank you for sharing that
that was yeah I you know what that's
that's different that you shared that
one and and it's not normally we hear
just you know straightforward praise
reports and we thank God for it but that
was beautiful that was really and I'll
tell you specifically why that's
particularly uh beautiful to me you know
amiron mentioned a moment ago about the
Men's Ministry and how we deal with some
of the things that perhaps she you know
felt that maybe women don't understand
and you know what maybe on the other
hand they would understand but one of
the struggles for men is we keep things
under wraps and we want to keep things
to ourselves and we're learning that
there's strength and vulnerability and
we're learning to open up and we're
learning to lead upon one another I see
a lot of the men in the chat brother
Robert I see you there in the chat
brother Trevor I saw you brother uh
Elder Robert Plant we are definitely
praying about your situation in your MRI
that's coming up and just brother you
know thank y'all so much brother Clint
there and and I saw last week brother
Robert invited more men to come come and
and and join us but uh what a beautiful
unfolding you know so am praise God for
that uh wanted to also send a a happy
anniversary out to brother Ross and
sister Gina they will be celebrating
their 37th wedding anniversary tomorrow
Lord willing they were going to come on
with us today but uh they decided to get
all the way out there Way Off the Grid I
mean so far off the grid they couldn't
even get internet connection so that's
pretty far out there but uh praise God
for them they're a blessing to us we
want to be a blessing to them want to
send them some love and a shout out that
whenever they get where they can play
back today's broadcast know that you we
are with you you are with us and in our
hearts and in our prayers happy
anniversary happy anniversary indeed
happy anniversary indeed and listen um
today it's standing in for Ross and Gina
as just some as two of our anchors and
we are so thankful for them they always
come in and pray for us they always here
with us you know such a support becomes
such a gift to this church such a pillar
and such a positive influence you know
those people that when they come into
the room you know they change the
atmosphere with just positivity and love
and that is brother Danny Clark and
sister jackan clark they're going to be
leading us to the throne of grace today
in innoc his prayer so bless you as you
come beloved we thank God for you as
[Music]
always amen amen amen amen bless you
both we love you both thank youen yes
and happy Sabbath to each and every one
of our folks online it's we're it's just
a pleasure it's a privilege let me say
it's a privilege prayer is a privilege
amen amen amen to be able to part
partner with you you know we've we've
learned so much about
prayer in the last year and and I think
the most significant thing that I have
learned is that we're not just praying
for you but we're as Prayer Warriors and
I and I believe I speak on behalf of all
of our prayer warriors we've learned
that we're not just praying for you
we're praying for you we're praying with
you we're in the trenches with you
during your struggles during in your
battles and we're taking them on so you
are not walking alone praise God is it
amen yes yes it's it's just so amazing
how God will open up your understanding
as to what he has called us to do you
know and and I think that every special
ops prayer call every prayer we you know
we find ourselves boy we're we're there
we're right there we're we we're at
attention we're praying we're we're
before God right on
and and and it's you know and prayer
could be it's it's a Warfare it can be a
Warfare but you are not in this battle
alone praise and thanks God you have a
prayer team that holds up the Blood
Stained Banner amen amen amen praise God
thank you my lovely wife who is feeling
better thank you you're welcome God
bless you it's always good to be here
with you but saying she hit it right on
the head we believe in the power of
prayer and the privilege of prayer so we
won't detain you we'll go be about God's
business and uh we'll begin our prayer
uh per time today together so let us go
to the Lord in prayer amen Heavenly
Father we thank you again Lord as my
wife so eloquently spoke Lord it is a
privilege and a honor and father we
thank you for the privilege and power of
prayer father you've given us you've
given us this uh uh ability to
Faithfully cry out to you Lord and
father we do it with trust Faith and
Hope hope Lord as we lift up these
prayers and on your people today I'm
asking you to have mercy upon every
petition Lord anoint the lips Lord and
request Lord at every prayer that goes
up Lord we know that you hear them
Father and we trust in your promises
Lord in Jesus name your word says come
to me all you who are weary and burdened
and I will give you rest amen father
thank you thank you for that Assurance
thank you for that promise amen and
father I lift up uh our sister Candace
buts Lord we just pray and thank you
Lord for her uh to trust in the prayer
press in the promises of God as we lift
her up to you today Lord she's asking
for uh prayer for her job father uh for
her finances Lord and for her uh recent
diagnosis so Lord we just pray that you
go before her Lord and and uh and
provide for her Lord we pray for her
healing and whatever she needs in
healing Lord we lift that up to you
right now and in the name of Jesus
father for her finances Lord we ask that
you provide for her every need father
we're asking because when we Faithfully
ask father you hear us Lord and we know
that you hear this prayer Lord and that
she is being faithful to you father I
pray in the name of Jesus plead the
blood of Jesus over her finances her
circumstances and every aspect of her
life in Jesus name I pray amen praise
God for sister Esther Esther Lita white
oh we're praising your name today thank
you Lord for the blessings that you have
blessed her with today Jes father
continue to heal and watch over her and
bless her Lord in the precious name of
Jesus Lord thank you Lord thank you for
uh for uh for her health Lord and Lord
I'm sure she is just praising you right
now and father I just pray you continue
your Divine Healing Lord to be upon her
in Jesus name I pray Lord and father I
Just Want to Thank You Lord For for uh
pastor Pastor Rister Lord I just put him
on my list today Lord I just lift him up
to you today Lord continue to bless his
ministry use him bless him Lord and even
his new program that he's coming forth
Lord I just feel led to pray for him
today and thank you for how you using
him in the body of Christ Lord he has a
message you given him uh uh anointed him
Lord to go forth with a word Lord bless
the young people and all of us Lord so I
pray for his ministry and Him Father uh
continue to watch and guide and lead him
in Jesus name amen thank you Lord I
continue to lift up our brother Trevor
Lord continue to provide for Him Father
praying that you hear his cry Lord keep
him close Lord and assure him father
that he is not alone father not alone
with you and not alone with his brothers
and sisters father lifting up his family
in the name of Jesus father put your
hands up on him Lord Heal him touch him
Lord in the name of Jesus I thank you
for hearing and answering that prayer in
Jesus name amen I think that's so I
think amen lifting up sister uh in the
prayer we lifting up brother dos and I
just or our dos and uh father we just
lift that petition up before you in the
name of Jesus you Lord you're able
praying that you provide all of their
needs according to your riches and glor
glory and father um you are the source
that provide the resources so we lord we
we we go past the resources to the very
source of the resources you own
everything a Catal the Thousand Hills is
yours the earth and the fullness thereof
is yours so father send resources for
our brothers send Lord the help your
word set to call on me and I will answer
and show you Great and Mighty things
that you know not of father I just want
to take a little time out just to pray
for immigrants I know Lord that some may
be fearful some may be anxious God and
and and Lord I just want to pray over
the situation and the circumstances
because God you are the all power for
God and there is nothing too hard for
you Lord you are the god that move that
you Lord you move uh Power you you you
move leaders in and you move them out
and you lead them out but even the ones
you you move in Lord you're able to to
orchestrate you're able to navigate Lord
the circumstan of situations in life to
even bring about certain situations uh
certain answers to prayer so God we call
on that God today that Sovereign God
that all powerful God that even even
Lord uh uh the Earthly uh Powers uh if
you will the Earthly Powers God have to
bow to your uh to your will Lord they
have to subject themselves their will
even to your will so God I lift up these
immigrants for for you Lord all those
for whatever the situation is whatever
the circumstances is this prayer is not
limited to that I'm lifting them all up
Lord you know each situation each
circumstance and father we're crying out
to you for these people for are yours
father hear their C cry rescue them Lord
in their circumstances rescue them Lord
in their situations rescue Lord even if
you have to change the winds in which
direction they're blowing to bring about
Lord their rescue we're just asking you
God to rescue them in the name of Jesus
and brother plant we this morning we are
combining our prayers and our faith with
yours father he's up for a procedure
next Friday and God we're claim it by
faith right now in the name of of of
Jesus uh favorable reports God that it
will come back good thank you God in
advance for hearing that prayer and
answering that prayer father we lift up
sister uh sister Hattie she wanted Lord
uh she has since the fires have started
in California but Lord let me just S
stand back let me just pray for that
group of people father we lift them up
we lift them up God and ask you to heal
heal them Lord bind up their wounds and
heal their broken hearts because Lord
doesn't matter where they're rich poor
in between they have uh been uh given a
death Uh u a blow father and and there
are emotions that's involved their uh
mental their psyche is involved in this
God there's finances there's loss father
we pray in the name of Jesus help them
God strengthen them God and remind them
that you are bigger than the fires
you're bigger than the lost but you're
the kind of God that Lord you will give
them double and some sometimes times
triple sometimes H hundredfold for their
troubles God that you're a God that know
how to step in God and whatever it is
Lord you have a way of working all
things every situation every
circumstance no matter how fatal it
seems you have a way of working it all
out for our good and glorifying Your
Name Lord and getting the glory out of
every situation and so father we lift up
Sister Hattie father we're praying for
she's she's feeling some of the effects
or the um uh the residual effects Lord
of all of the fires uh and is showing up
in her body father we're praying in the
name of Jesus father that you touch her
body relieve her that cough God I pray
God that you that you bring a halt to
that bleeding Lord with that mucus
coming out father I just pray that you
impress upon her some good natural
remedies that she can take to prevent it
Lord as well as to uh uh to promote the
healing of the flushing of the things
contaminantes in her body that's causing
uh that's causing this condition father
we pray in the name of Jesus because you
have an answer for everything there is
an answer so father just breathe Lord
just breathe upon her body and bring it
into Wellness Lord in the name of Jesus
father we're lifting up uh the prayer
request for sunshine I love that name
Sunshine it reminds me of the s o n that
does shine on his people hallelujah so
father we she's looking she needs a job
and she's also praying for a best friend
who who has cancer and Lord and prayers
for Donald father we lift up these
petitions Lord as as our sister Tia May
says I love to pray you know them by
number Lord you know everything about
them even the very hairs on their heads
are counted so father we lift up these
situations before before you you have a
job Lord for her a job with her name
written on it a job that's conducive
Lord to her ex situations and of
circumstances and Lord a fool full time
job that provides uh the monetary
resources that could that is needed so
father we're praying that open a door
that no man can close and close all
doors that no man can open that that she
should not even walk through father
we're putting this in your in your hands
asking you God to make a way where she
may not right now she may feels there is
no way but Lord you have a way and
father we also praying for the friends
God even cancer is not too big for you
father we put this in your hands we're
praying you God that you just move Lord
in these situations and you in the
circumstances father praying that you
strengthen praying God that you rescue
praying that you heal in the name of
Jesus father we're lifing up uh p uh
sister pan uh pansy's request before you
to keep her family in prayer Lord
especially her son onza and the friend a
great father we bring this family before
your room your your throne room of grace
and mercy father ask you to heal them
everywhere they hurt father praying that
you bind them together in love and that
love is Christ Jesus the word said a
three string cord is not easily broken
and Lord when Christ is the middleman in
that in that cord it cannot be broken so
father just praying oh Lord in the name
of Jesus by the power of your Holy
Spirit move in this family Lord move in
their lives move in their hearts move in
their circumstances and their situations
bring bring them God into a loving
Covenant relationship with you Lord that
that your name would be glorified that
your name will be honored lifting up
sister brette and her requests God she's
praying for her the same thing her
family Lord that they grow in a
knowledge and understanding Lord so that
we will that they will not be deceived
Lord and I I pray this not just for
sister Vette but for us all father help
us God help us God to have a hunger and
thirst for your word word that is
unquenchable am father I pray that you
give us a desire to get in your word and
to stay in your word give us a hunger
and thirst for prayer because these are
the tools Lord that we're going to need
at such a time as this Lord help us to
know how to search the scriptures for in
them Lord we will find peace and rest
and answers oh God to that which is and
is to come father I just pray for sister
Brett's family Lord strengthen their
understanding help them God to stand
firm on the on your word in the name
ofes in Jesus firmly rooted and
established upon that Solid Rock that's
your foundation God that Foundation that
is unbreakable that Foundation Lord that
cannot be uh be destroyed and that solid
rock that we're talking about that
Foundation is Christ Jesus because he is
the word from Genesis to Revelation that
beautiful love story of Salvation that
beautiful love story of how you are
rescued you came to send your son to
rescue your people to save your people
to the deliver your people in the name
of Jesus lifting up Sister matina maa's
request God and she's praying oh Father
in the name of Jesus for family members
from the Antioch School that suffered
loss of lives two students oh God one
who killed the others have mercy father
have mercy Lord have mercy father have
mercy oh God on these parents Lord
because both parents lost in this
situation Lord the parent whose son
performed the act as well as the parents
whose Sons Lord were brutally killed
from it father help in the name of Jesus
help us oh God the word tell us that the
thief comes but to kill steal and
destroy but Christ came came right back
around in the next scripture said but I
come so that you may have life and that
more abundantly oh Father rescue your
people Lord from the hands of the enemy
Lord I pray that you protect them Lord
from the pestilence and the F the foul
Fowler who comes to destroy destroy in
the name of Jesus father he comes to
take away our joy Lord to Rob and steal
of us our peace because he know when he
gets that God that that that we'll start
fearing and that fear leads is torment
and that torment leads to doubt and
ultimately he want us to doubt you and
your word and your love for us father in
the name of Jesus in the name of Jesus
rebuke this Lord in the name of Jesus
rise up oh God and let your enemies be
destroyed rise up oh God and let the
enemies of your people be destroyed in
the name of Jesus help your people save
this Lord I pray for the school I pray
for the children who witnessed this
father I pray for their me their psyche
I pray for their emotions oh God and
Lord even in this even than this you
have a way God to get some Glory out of
it and God we stand on that but I pray
that you heal these hearts Lord Heal
these Hearts bind up these wounds Lord
and menend them in the name of Jesus and
sister Michelle Lord I I I I saw your
your your request Lord of U of U of that
anxiety and and you know what the word
of God tell us to be anxious for nothing
but in everything by prayer and
supplication with Thanksgiving to let
our request be be made known to God and
the peace of God which surpasses all
understanding will guard our hearts and
Minds through Christ Jesus so father I
want to I want to lift up our sister
before you Lord you know the situation
that she experienced you even know the
root cause for this experience and
father I'm praying that you uproot the
root cause of this exper uh of of of
this anxiousness in the name of Jesus
father let your child have peace let her
have uh joy in the name of Jesus show
and lead her Lord how to trust in you
father we are praying for healing from
anything that would make her feel
anxious God In The Name of Jesus you
want your people to be whole complete
trusting in you father so we lift it up
have your way God Have Your Way in the
name of Jesus we pray God we thank you
for what you doing we thank you God for
what you all you're always there you
always hear our prayer you always hear
our cry God and we are grateful uh
grateful Lord grateful to you for this
father we lift up our beloved Pastor
Lord and his family his wife sister
tante your precious maid sir servant and
your P your your precious man servant
father we bring them before the throne
of grace and mercy in the name of Jesus
father we lift up uh sister Erica his
mom we lift up brother Ronnie his dad we
lift up Veronica uh and the children
Sarai Judah and Savana father where we
lift up the entire the entire family the
nieces the nephews we lift up all of
brother Sea's friends uh uh people that
acquaintances that knew him were that
were impacted by his life father we pray
for them God In The Name of Jesus father
praying that you we that you hold Pastor
up praying that you strengthen him God
at such a time as this father when he is
weak you make him strong because his
strength is in you father this is the
time that you you you when your word
says that you will bear them up on
eagles wings and calls them Lord to ride
the storms of light Lord bear him up in
the name of Jesus bear up sister tante
in the name of Jesus bear them up God
and may your power be revealed God may
your strength be exposed God come in God
and have your way bind up their wounds
oh Father bind up their wounds and
menend these broken hearts God you're
bigger Lord You're greater God and we
know that you're yet in control and
father we thank you because in this we
can have confidence that regardless God
regardless this is your man servant this
is your maid servant and God he knows
the mission
yes he knows the mission you made sure
that and God when you're ready for him
you're going to speak in such a way that
he knows that he knows that he's knows
it's time to be about that mission God
he knows the mission sister tante know
the mission God that you for ordained
that you had already given because God
you called him to carry it out and God
we thank you that we can Relish in this
fact that you will Empower that you will
strengthen that God you would do what is
needed to do to ensure that the mission
Goes Forth so thank you God lord I just
ask wrap your big warm arms around this
family and hug them tight huj squeeze
them God let them feel your presence let
them feel your strength oh God In The
Name of Jesus because you promis never
to leave not forsake them Father we
thank you because in this we have
confidence that you love them with an
everlasting love
oh Lord in the name of Jesus Sarai you
love her Judah Savana God and S sister
Veronica God you know their future and
maybe they may feel some uncertainty but
God you're already there in their future
and for us all we don't know what the
future holds but we know who holds our
future God that our future is in your
hands and we're trusting you God you in
that future already provided already
made way that was needed God and we
thank you Father for that thank you for
your goodness because if it wasn't for
the goodness of God we would be consumed
but but God your goodness is too good to
let us be consumed even though we may
grieve and cry you're too good to allow
us to be consumed thank you God thank
you Father thank you for your love thank
you for your grace Your Grace thank you
for your mercy thank you God that that
we are your people and you are our Good
Shepherd God and you will never leave
your sheep to go astray Lord I just pray
all of these in the name name of Christ
your son and our Lord and
savior thank you for your mercy feel of
Praise right now thank you Lord for the
word and the prayers that went up today
Lord thank you for hearing and answering
these prayers today Father I lift up our
brother our man Ser to bring the word
today Lord we bless him Lord we lift him
up to you today fill him with the Holy
Spirit may your word come with
conviction Lord ministering to the
people's Heart Lord use him for your
glory Lord in the precious name of Jesus
I pray amen
amen
amen amen we do praise God for those
beautiful Warriors and for leading us to
the throne of grace today we have a
special
announcement um earlier there was a
slide shared for Sean's celebration of
life and we just just wanted to let you
know that there has been a time change
that was not reflected on that slide
everyone is invited to attend the live
stream of Sean's celebration of life but
it will begin at 900 a.m. eastern
standard time not 9:30 so we didn't want
you to miss the first half an hour so
again Sean's celebration of life will be
at 900 a.m. eastern standard time and
that's 6: a.m. Pacific Standard time so
I just wanted to uh let you guys know
there will be more information on the
live stream link and all of that coming
soon so thank you so much amen amen
[Music]
I shall wear a
crown I shall wear a
[Music]
crown when it's all
over when it's all over
I shall
wear a
crown I shall wear a
crown when it's all
over then it's all over
I'm going to put on
my tell the
story how I made it
over I'm going to put on my
RO tell the
story how I made
it
over
soon I
get
[Music]
home
so I care
[Music]
I shall
see his
face I shall see his
face
oh when he hits all
over when and it's all
[Music]
over I'm going to put on my
robe
tell the
story how I made it
[Music]
over okay I'm going to put on my RO
tell the story how I I made it
over I'm going to put on my
RO
tell the
story how I made it
over yeah
yeah I going to put on my
RO tell the story how I made it it
over
yeah I am going to put on my
RO tell the story how I made it
over I'm going to put on my RO
tell the
story how I made it
over
soon I
get
home so
[Music]
hi
yeah
home oh
yes
s
i yeah
[Music]
Hallelujah come on somebody you can put
that right in the chat
Hallelujah the song said I'm gonna put
on my robe and tell the story of how I
made it over I love it when he begin to
sing when it's all over I don't know who
selected the song today but I tell you
what glory to God what a powerful
message that is how many of you going to
tell the story what's your story gonna
be like when you get to Glory when you
hear that phrase when it's all over it
what all of what the
pain the heartache the struggles the
trial the disappointment the let UPS let
Downs break-ins breakouts when it's all
over Hallelujah somebody don't we have
something to look forward to in glory
and thinking about Heaven's diary how
many you want to make it there how many
want to make that Journey come on
somebody and say Amen today thank you
for that beautiful worship and for that
beautiful song That Just prepares our
hearts to receive the word of God today
when it's all over but today we have a
message and our message today is simply
entitled now oh yeah we look forward to
Glory when it's all over but our message
today is simply
entitled now what about now Lord show me
what to do with my now because this is
where I am this is where we are and this
is all we have right now is this moment
today is January 25th
2025 we will never see this moment and
time again 12:50 to be exact
350 if you're back on the East Coast two
if you're in central time maybe if
you're in the beautiful island of cura
and down in the island maybe maybe maybe
it's 450 whatever in this moment in time
right now we'll never see it again may
God teach us how to seize this moment
and make the most of it God what did you
bring us to this hour for right now why
are why am I here why did I come through
all that mess how did I get when the
bullets were flying why didn't they
pierce my skull why not me why am I here
now God help me Lord to hear you to see
you to cooperate with you and to make it
through this now because after this it's
next and so when I get to my next i w
want to look back and said if I would
have should have could have I want to
know that I did what I needed to do in
my now so that my next when I get there
will be a blessing can somebody say amen
that's our message today now Lord show
me what to do
now what to do now you know Saints um
I'm not particularly interested today in
giving you a word that will entertain
you or word that will make you just say
um or maybe that well that was a cool
Insight oh that was deep not interested
in that we need a word today that's
gonna stick with us see if if I have
some ideas or some thoughts even about
the scriptures and about the word of God
you know my thoughts and my ideas they
just passing you know but if God Gets
behind this thing today and he says
something we're talking about the God
that spoke planets into existence and
they're still sitting right there to
this day see when God says something
something happens and it makes a
difference and so what we want today is
a word that's going to stick with you a
word that's going to pop up in your
heart and mind when you get into some of
that when it's all over stuff when you
get into some of that mess and some of
that Madness and when you ready to show
out act up and fly off the handle we
need a word that's going to pop up in
our mind and remind us of who we are and
who he is we need a word that will show
us what to do now what do I do now when
the bottoms falling out of it what do I
do now Lord when when when when when the
bills are due what do I do now God when
trouble's all around me on all sides
what do I do now Lord when my faith is
being challenged what do I do now God
when my heart is broken what do I do now
Lord what do I do
now and so Saints we're going to pray
that God will give us that word today
will speak in our hearts today a word
that will make us toss and turn on our
bed wrestle with it be challenged with
it and change our lives forever in Jesus
name and so God we thank you for
bringing us to January 25
2025 Lord we do not take this moment
lightly we are here and we give you the
glory it is only by your grace that we
are here Lord and so we bless you and we
praise you in Jesus name thank you for
the gift of prayer that we get to draw
near to you you said if we draw near to
you you will draw near to us and so Lord
thank you so much for this hour thank
you for those that are watching thank
you for those who will watch Lord God
breathe on this word today in Jesus
mighty name show us what to do now
amen well praise the Lord Saints you
know um the Lord started talking to me
about this concept of now that I want to
uh minister to you today um he started
talking to me about it few weeks ago and
and I I be honest with you I really
wasn't sure how I was going to even
begin to set this thing up and begin to
discuss it and talk about it because it
was really just simple at the at the
time but you know how it is when you
stand in the word of God and you you
start digging deep uh brother Danny and
sister Jackie and you start getting to
that fiber things just start growing you
know you get into the genetics of the
scriptures as Pastor Myer teaches us in
photo theology things just start growing
you start seeing connections everywhere
you got Lord I don't know if I'm gonna
have time this thing getting too big the
Lord just says look just deliver the
message and I'll do the rest because
folk when you go and start searching the
word of God and you start meditating on
this thing God's going to give you your
own Revelation because he got something
to say to you personally for your own
life so anyway I didn't really know how
I was going to get going but then a few
days ago me and sister Amar decided we
were going to sit here and uh get into
the word of God and we're going to read
and um we decided to read the Gospel of
John that day we I think we're having
lunch and and and typically like it is
with me and Amar you know we sit down we
might read about five verses and that's
as far as we get and we gonna sit there
for about two hours going and we think
wow we didn't get anywhere but this time
in John we did get to at least I think
about verse 35 and as we began to you
know meditate in the word and study and
talk about different things the spirit
of the Lord was showing us
um I think I begin to realize I said
wait a minute Lord I think you giv us
the setup you giv us the introduction to
this message because Amara said
something she said you know what before
Jesus even came along God spoke to John
about him and showed him what was going
to happen and everything about who he
was and his baptism and I said yeah she
says wouldn't it be something just one
day you just um walking along and all of
a sudden God just revealed that and as
she was saying that the Lord says oh no
no no it started long before that it
wasn't that way with John and so here's
what we began to do we started looking
at John's birth and what happened in
John and John's life with Zachariah his
father when he was in the temple and the
Lord begin to announce the birth of John
and so this first slide was where we
went I believe we went to Luke uh
chapter 1 and zachariah's in the temple
and here's what happen Saints and so
we're in Luke 1:
13-16 if you have your Bibles beautiful
if you do not have your Bibles um then
we'll be
uh there the word of God declares and
there appeared unto him an angel of the
Lord standing in the right side of the
altar of incense and when Zachariah saw
him he was trouble and fear fell upon
him the word of God goes goes on to
read but the angel said unto him fear
not Zachariah for thy prayer is heard
and thy wife Elizabeth shall bear thee a
son and thou shalt call his name John
and thou shalt have joy and gladness and
many shall rejoice at his birth for he
shall be great in the sight of the Lord
and shall drink neither wine nor strong
drink and he shall be filled with the
Holy Ghost even from his mother's womb
and many of the children of Israel shall
he turn
to the Lord their God and
so John's now did not begin on the day
he saw Jesus and declared Behold the
Lamb of God which taketh away the sin of
the world John's Destiny and John's call
and John's election began in the heart
of God when God had a design a plan and
a purpose for the life of John and so as
we were thinking about this I began to
realize wait a minute this same thing
God said said about someone else that we
know who had a great call upon his life
and that was Paul and so when we look at
Galatians chapter 1 15- 16 here's what
Paul said about his call Paul said when
it please God who separated me from my
mother's womb and called me by his grace
to reveal his son in me that I might
preach him among the Heathen immediately
I conferred not with flesh and blood so
here is Paul again he's saying look my
now actually started when God chose to
separate me from my mother's womb and
called me by his grace and so you know
how it is Saints as you begin to study
the word of God and you get into the
scriptures and you put yourself into the
text and you're listening for what the
Lord is
saying the spirit of God gonna start
leading you to things that you didn't
think about when you first started so
right away after we're talking about
John and me and Emer were talking about
Paul who do you think next popped up in
our head what who popped up next someone
with a great call on their life similar
type call calling it was Jeremiah look
at what the Lord said to Jeremiah when
he called him in Jeremiah chapter 1 he
says
um then the word of the Lord came unto
me saying before I formed thee in the
belly I knew thee and before thou camest
forth out of the womb I Sanctified thee
and I ordained thee a prophet unto the
Nations then I said a lord God behold I
cannot speak for I am a child but the
Lord said unto me say not I am a child
for Thou shalt go to all that I shall
send thee and whatsoever I command thee
Thou shalt speak be not afraid of their
faces for I am with thee to deliver Thee
sayth the Lord praise God praise God for
his word and so what we have three great
callings three great men of God for some
of them they are Our Heroes of Faith
Jeremiah uh uh Paul uh uh John I mean
great great Great Men of God who we read
about we learn about we read their words
but I want you to see something that
came up next and this had to be the
beauty of of God's goodness and God's
grace and God's call because you know
what Paul's not here right now his words
are the words that God gave him Jeremiah
is not here and neither is John the
Baptist but you and I are here right now
and what is God saying to us about our
call right now and so he led us to uh
the first epistle Paul's first epistle
to the Corinthians and I want you to see
what Paul said when he spoke to the
Corinthians and keep this in mind as
we're reading about the Corinthians I'll
come back to that in a minute let me
just read this 1 Corinthians chapter 1
verses 1 and two Paul called to be an
apostle of Jesus Christ through the will
of God and sustenance our brother unto
the Church of God which is at Corinth to
them that are Sanctified in Christ Jesus
called to be Saints with all that in
every place call upon the name of Jesus
Christ Our Lord both sister both theirs
and ours amen let's come back to the
screen for a moment let's talk a moment
about Corinth this is Paul's greeting to
the Corinthians and all of us are
familiar with some of the things that
were going on in the Corinthians church
so here it in in chapter three of course
you know Paul begins his his discussion
with Corinth and he and and you know we
can go through the whole epistle and
just pick out so many different things
that were going on there he identified
them as babes he says I can't speak to
you as spiritual men because you're as
babe so I got to give you milk instead
of meat there's divisions and strife
among you there were some uh uh
fornication and things going on there in
chapter five we even see when they got
into the church there were folk that
were using their spiritual gifts or
misusing them rather you know and he had
to let them know you know your gift is
about bringing glory to God and not unto
yourself I mean on and on and on we had
just so many different things going on
within that church at
Corinth mess some of that when it's all
over stuff was going on right there but
yet right here at the beginning of that
letter before we even find any of that
stuff out that Paul was aware of when he
wrote that letter the word of God says
that they are called to be
Saints in spite of all the mess and the
madness that was going on in that church
they were yet called to be Saints what
happened with the Corinthians that so
many there were missing out on there now
how is it that instead of doing what
they were called to do they were somehow
caught up in something else missing
their appointment with Destiny missing
their moment their now what's going on
in our lives that could possibly be
causing us to miss our now because I
will tell you Saints just like God's man
told Esther he says perhaps God has
brought you to the kingdom for such a
time as
this could this be your now Saints could
this be your opportunity to step out
into greatness could this be your
opportunity to rise up and be the leader
that God has called you to be whether it
be at your home in your job whether it
be in the church whether it be in
Ministry is this your time it won't help
to look around at other folk what
they're doing and how they may be
stumbling and how they may be feeling
and think that's going to bring you into
your success it will not
the only way for you and I to make the
most of our now and to seize this moment
is we need a strong point of reference
I'm gonna say that again Saints we need
a strong point of reference and I
believe what the word of God is trying
to tell us today is there are some
things going on that has distracted our
minds from our point of reference matter
of fact in First Corinthians chapter 7
verse 35 the apostle was talking to them
about marriage and just out of nowhere
he said you know what I would these
things I'm saying to you I'm saying to
you for for the beauty of the Lord and
that you would learn to attend unto the
Lord
without
distraction there are some distractions
that are causing us to miss our moment
matter of fact let's take a closer look
at what the angel said to Zachariah
about
John just some comparisons uh between
Paul and Jeremiah's call first of all I
noticed that when we were reading about
Paul in the Galatians he's he used two
words he used separated and he used the
word called but when Jeremiah spoke the
Lord used the word Sanctified or cadesh
which means to be set apart and ordained
something that God had established and
set in motion but when he gets to the
Corinthians he takes both of those
Concepts Sanctified from Jeremiah called
from Paul and he speaks all both of
those elements to the Corinthians and
he's telling them look it's not just
about what God was saying in my life or
in Jeremiah's life or in John's life but
this also applies to you this is about
you and God and God has something for
you watch this next slide that that that
we'll see about John the Baptist such a
powerful
thing Luke says in John in Luke chapter
1 verse1 15 and speaking of John the
Baptist he says for he shall be great in
the sight of the Lord and shall drink
neither wine nor strong drink and he
should be filled with the Holy Ghost
ruach Kadesh in Hebrew the set aart
Spirit even from his mother's womb this
is very important and very significant
to us beloved and here is why today as
we were listening to Back to
Basics Pastor anaton said something
really really powerful they said that
the whole world will be United under
that same Spirit the only ones who will
not be United on when the when the mark
of the when the when the beast's wound
is healed is the remnant they are Gods
set apart who SED that we are not going
to go along we're not going to get along
and we're not going to follow after this
Same Spirit there are all sorts of div
divisions and fractions and beliefs and
and we have people who don't say they
don't believe the atheist Pastor said
that you know they you you show it to me
I'll believe it but there's one thing
that is a common denominator amongst all
all those factions they all have
elements from that one Same Spirit the
spirit of the world and he used the
quote from Sister white and said that
you know Satan he'll be converted to the
modern H order of things because he
knows just what they need well in John
the Baptist the Lord was aware that this
Nazarene who was coming to do such a
great work in preparing the way of the
Lord which is exactly what we are called
to right now Saints of the most high God
Seventh Day Adventist we have been
called to prepare the way for the coming
of the Lord that same call that same
spirit that was upon John the Baptist
has called us to be set apart and so
what the instructions that the lord gave
to that angel was that listen there are
certain distractions and contaminants in
this world and we want you to know that
he needs to be set apart from that no
wine and no strong drink to enter into
him pastor this morning used an analogy
and I want to share that with you today
an analogy for example here's one of the
things that are contaminating in the
world I'll get back to the strong drink
in a minute but first let me tell you
about this in the spirit of the world
there are certain contaminants that are
designed to distract the people of God
from their mission sister Jackie why we
don't know the mission why we miss the
mission while we miss our moment and our
now first of all if we look at sports
Pastor use a sports analogy this morning
I want you to look at all the main
sports in the world today whether it be
football basketball baseball soccer
NASCAR whatever it is those were major
ones but they're other sports venues and
typically let's take baseball basketball
there's only like 10 players on the
court and maybe three or four referees
football 11 players on each side and
maybe four referees there but if you
look at these sports
stadiums with the few people we see on
the field or on the court
how many seats are in the
stand
thousands this practice in our culture
that so deeply inid in our culture and
so deeply ingrained is designed to make
the world observers rather than players
in the
game let's go to
entertainment only so much room on the
screen for an actor right and millions
are observing just
watching let's look at social media what
does it do keep us like this all day
observing
watching another Sports
analogy what do they drink John was the
angel said John not to drink strong
drink listen there's always a spiritual
parallel here there's another strong
drink you know in sports they like
Gatorade right you know what the drink
is the the the enemy is trying to give
us hater
Ray do you find that you feel a little
some something inside of you just feels
a little bit better when you're watching
somebody just fall on their face if
that's the case something wrong with you
because we ought to be celebrating the
victories of the other people we ought
to be happy to see someone else doing
good we ought to be happy to see our
brothers and sisters in the church we
don't we shouldn't fall into that trap
that Pastor talked to us about that crab
Theology of look I'm not going nowhere
and nobody else is going nowhere I'm in
my misery and I'm in this bucket I can't
crawl out and I'm not going to let
nobody else crawl up out of this hole
listen Saints we don't want that drink
we need to stay away from that drink
right there that drink right there will
could poison us and contaminate us we
want to be here to support one another
and love one another fervently as the
scripture says and as Jesus said in John
13 the world will know you my disciples
by the love you have one to another we
don't want that drink of hating that's
become a cultural Trend in in in in our
society can't stand to see nobody else
do good we like watching stars
fall about that by the
way the Isaiah the prophet Isaiah and I
don't have slides for these you're gonna
have to look this up yourself Isaiah
said in Isaiah chapter 8 he says I and
the children whom the Lord has given me
are for signs and wonders in Israel when
the Lord created the Moon and the Sun
and the stars in the sky you know what
he said they are they're for signs and
for Seasons when we read in Daniel 12: 3
and 4 it says that they who turn many to
righteousness shall be as the stars of
the firmament when God was trying to
give Abraham a concept of his
descendants and how numerous they would
be he took him out and told him look can
you count the stars in the sky if you
can then so can you count your
descendants you know who the real stars
are in this world it's us Saints and
we're not to be observers the world
ought to be watching us and we ought to
be doing something to keep their
attention we ought to be pointing them
to Jesus we're the star Stars we're not
to be observing no stars and that's what
the enemy is trying to do with this
strong drink he's selling in the world
make us observers rather than players in
the game come on somebody now is your
time now is your time I was listening to
brother uh Pastor loamy this morning and
as I was listening I could hear the Lord
saying see that ter you know when I was
in prison I read a book by Dr Miles
Monroe entitled becoming a leader now he
wasn't an Adventist but he spoke a lot
about leaders ship and and and and as I
was coming into present truth I was I
learned a lot from this brother you know
and some of his quotes were awesome
about
leaders that he said that all of us have
within us the capacity to be a leader
but only those certain ones of us have
the courage the courage to cultivate
that and there was just so many quotes
that he said about that and so I started
thinking about what Pastor Lami was
saying this morning about being able to
connect with the younger generation
being able to connect with the younger
generation Saints God has called some of
us to stand up and be that leader that
makes that difference to be that leader
that that that can give those answers
that confront those answer those
questions about addiction those
questions about God I love what he said
God's Not Afraid of those questions that
are asked there is a reason why but only
those leaders only those leaders who
have established have discovered and
found what their true point point of
reference is which is what we're about
to talk about in a minute only those
will stand up and seize the moment and
step out step into there now right now
only those will step out of the stands
and quit being observers and watching
some people talk to me a lot of times
about I would like to see this type of
ministry in the church well I would like
to see that type of ministry well the
church probably needs
this possibly God is telling you I need
you to step up and do it if you see it
every s I have been with Pastor Myers
he's always been the type of brother
that would say listen we need people
that will step up and be ministers step
up and to start Ministries he's always
had that in mind way back with house
fires even more he's always trying to
raise up leaders God has called us to be
leaders all of us to lead can we say
Amen
somebody can we say Amen but you know
the thing is I want to ask you a
question right
now who are
you
really and where are you
now where are you in your spiritual walk
with God where are you in your life
where are you in your spiritual growth
and development who are you and where
are
you now I know when I ask you that
question that audio and that videot tape
just starts running
why because your answer whatever it is
it's going to come from some point of
reference that you have in your mind and
in your heart what is that point of
reference let's make it a little more
plain Let's Take a Walk let's take a
field trip today let's go all the way
back to the
beginning let's go back to the garden
and hear that question asked to the
first man Adam
Genesis chapter 3: 8-10 let's read this
together the Bible says and speaking of
Adam and Eve and they heard the voice of
the Lord God Walking In The Garden in
the cool of the day and Adam and his
wife hid themselves from the presence of
the Lord God amongst the Trees of the
garden and the Lord God called unto Adam
and said unto him where art thou and he
said I heard thy voice in the garden and
I was was afraid because I was naked and
I hid
myself we're very familiar with this
story we're very familiar with this
passage but in the theater of your mind
beloved sometimes in order for the word
of God to speak to us deeply and really
impact us we need to put ourselves on
the scene and put ourselves in the text
let's put ourselves in the situation God
ain't just talking to act
he talking to us and I'll say this right
now on Adam's behalf we have something
Adam didn't have right there we have a
point of reference we have opportunity
for a great great point of reference
that Adam did not have you know if you
really look at that and think about it
you know what Adam's answer was well
what had happened was when God asked
Adam where are you he he basically said
well what had happened was you know why
because the only point of reference Adam
had was what he had
done what had happened
was that was the only point of reference
he had was well when God asked him in
his now where are you now his mind went
back to the past what had happened what
he had done I ain't just saying this I
know this because I used to be a Houdini
I knew about disappearing most of my
disappearing act because I had done
something I had no business doing when I
came to living Mana we noticed something
there were so many women in the church
and hardly any men why was the man
disappearing I know about disappearing
look I done enough wrong it caused me to
disappear for 25 years and nobody see
brother Terry 25 years I disappeared and
some folk leaving the church now because
something they
undone but God wants to give us a
greater point of reference so we won't
find oursel hiding in mess hiding in
Madness hiding in chaos hiding in
division hiding in Strife God wants to
show us some of the very things we are
hiding from him are the things he
desires and longs to heal beloved
everything we're hiding from him he
wants to heal everything we're hiding
from him he has made provision of for
before he put us here on this rock
floating in the middle of space beloved
our God is Alpha and Omega he is Jehovah
Gyra the Great provider just like
Abraham somebody watching coming up on
the Rough Side of the Mountain your
provisions on the other side I love what
sister Jackie brought to us from the
spirit of Prophecy the other week when
we surrender and submit ourselves to the
service of the Lord there is no position
you hear me somebody no
position that you can find yourself in
even if it's what had happened was even
if it was something you done there's no
position you can find yourself in that
God has not made provision vision
for come on come on somebody he can get
you out and you talking to the man that
been to the bottom looking up at the
bottom below the bottom I know the God
we serve can save I know the God we
serve can heal I know the God we serve
can touch and deliver transform and turn
you around I know he can and he wants us
to know that because if we don't know
that we're not going to do the right
thing and our now now now but you know
sometimes you need to see it in somebody
else's life you know during um the 10
days of prayer some powerful stuff
happen because you know our our power
Wednesday format our weekly prayer
service is formated after the 10 days of
prayer we enjoy the 10 days of prayer so
much that we literally format it power
Wednesday and you may not recognize that
unless you come there often and you look
at it oh well this just like the 10 days
of prayer is it is and the reason you
know being is because you know we see
God moving and he's hearing and
answering prayer and so we we do thank
him for what he's doing here at Living
Mana started on prayer but you know
confession
time sometimes we've noticed confession
time can be the quietest time it can be
seem kind of awkward you know sometimes
but I want to say this this year during
the 10 days of prayer the most powerful
time for me was the time of confession
God's people were pouring their hearts
out some people were naming some of them
sins that most folk hide don't talk
about in public they were saying some
things because we always our
facilitators and our prayer leaders
always give a quiet time in the
beginning of confession for you between
you and God but I'm G to tell you when
folk get desperate and they really want
to get a hold of God they G put that
stuff out there and lay it out I don't
care what you think about me I don't
care if I got to let my hair down I
don't care what I got to do I don't care
if I got to get ugly I don't care if
snot got to roll out my nose or whatever
I got to get this mess out of my life I
got to make room for Jesus I love that
and so when I started seeing and hearing
that I said somebody trying to get a
hold of God in here somebody mean
business with God on this night and so
what was happening is I'm sitting there
and I'm thinking Lord somebody in here
putting words to some of the stuff I
want to confess and that was so powerful
Saints it is powerful when the Church of
God began to confess sins before the
Lord and just lay stuff out their faults
and needs and Lord change me Transform
Me Lord fix me God heal me help me to
get right in you that's a beautiful
thing prayer warriors love it and so
seeing that in other folks lives when
when the world sees our vulnerability
when the world sees that we're keeping
it real and not faking and putting on
mask and facade then the world want to
follow us because listen y'all like I
said in the beginning like the Lord had
us to say we're the Stars we're the
signs and wonders that the world ought
to be observing and it's time for us to
come out of the stands and stand up and
represent our God Saints we can do it
with this strong point of ref reference
let's look at it in the life of Joshua
and so God will give us examples just
like he did on 10 days of prayer let's
look at it in the life of Joshua look at
this thing I I love this thing that
happened with
Joshua so we took a field trip to
Genesis just now in the theater of your
mind let's go to Jericho all right I
need you to do this with me we're going
up to Jericho right now we're standing
there it's not January 25 2025 it's now
whatever date that was Joshua was
standing there our now is right now at
Jericho all right and God's getting
ready to talk let's listen now after the
death of Moses the servant of the Lord
it came to pass that the Lord spake unto
Joshua the son of nun Moses's Min
Minister saying Moses my servant is dead
now therefore arise go over this Jordan
thou and all this people unto the land
which I do give them even the children
of Israel oh don't miss this now Saints
every place that the soul of your foot
shall tread upon that have I given unto
you as I said unto
Moses every place God is speaking now
because remember you ain't in your house
you're not at your table you're not in
your car you're not in the living room
you're not in the bedroom you're now
standing at Jericho and God is is saying
right now every place that the soul of
your foot shall future tread upon that
have I pass given unto you you've heard
me say this so many times we are
anatomically designed to go that way all
of us have a
past all of us in Christ Jesus by the
grace of God are headed to a future
somewhere we're headed there but what we
have right now is our now and we're
standing here now and God is
saying your confidence your boldness the
courage you need to move forward to be
the best you can be to be all I've
called you to be has absolutely nothing
to do with what you did or where you
from or where you're going or what folks
say it's what I have done God told
Joshua he says every place that the soul
of your foot shall tread upon if you got
fear about going into the future if you
got fear about what happening for you in
the future if you looking at your
circumstances and where you from and
what's happening I want you to keep this
is going to be your point of reference
right here that have I given to you
already that's our anchor not what we
have done what other folks have done but
what God has done isn't that too
simple isn't that
simple that is what our anchor is to be
Saints our only point of reference needs
to be what the Lord has said what What
the Lord Has Done and What the Lord Has
accomplished is it
enough is it enough you know when I was
in
prison there was a spirit in prison like
we were talking earlier about the spirit
of the world the spirit of the world is
designed to get us all swept up in it so
we will miss our divine appointment so
we will miss our calling so we will miss
our election so we'll miss what we were
Sanctified and set apart for that's
what's the design of the spirit of the
world when I was in prison I'm going to
tell you a story about a minute but when
I was in prison
um you know there's this thing we called
institutionalization and those who
allowed themselves to get caught up in
institutionalization either resolved to
live the rest of their lives in prison
they were either resolved to live the
rest of their lives in and out of prison
or in in violence in crime in corruption
in lostness in depression in despair in
hopelessness in poverty just giving up
Institution
and then when they come out many men who
didn't do anything about uh if you
weren't intentional let me say this if
you wanted to miss that state of
institutionalization you had to be very
intentional about your programming you
had to be very intentional about getting
on your knees and getting before God not
wasting time sitting in front of the TV
and sitting at the at them tables
playing games or hanging around out
there with them brothers telling one
another a whole bunch of lies about what
they used to do and what they used to
how they used to be but you had to be
about your business you had to take
advantage of every class every vocation
everything you could do to transform
your life in other words you had to be
on a crusade for change and you had to
mean it or otherwise that thing would
just get you caught up in it and you
would go
nowhere there was another thing called
institutional remission and some people
could get in there and just adapt you
know humans have such an amazing ability
to adapt the drug addict could sit in
there for several years and never use
any drugs in a minute the door open
right back to it the thief can sit in
there and keep his hand to himself not
bothering other people stuff and he knew
better in there because they didn't play
about that type of thing get right out
and got to steal something from
somebody you
see institutional real mission in other
words you had to be real about it in
other words you got to be a real
Christian in other words you got to mean
business with Jesus can't be in here
playing no games come on somebody come
on somebody and so we had to keep it
real 100 or else you would find yourself
caught up in that corrupt
institutionalization amen that is the
attitude we had to have we had to have
and so one of the things that came to my
mind I said I was going to tell you a
story about this you know because uh
earlier when I was talking about the
spirit of the world
sometimes we can allow ourselves to get
a sip of that wine and we start thinking
well it's just not so bad you know
they're not
really the world's not that bad you it's
okay to Dil and dail in this it's okay
to do this a little bit of this listen
to me church militant we are at War
whether you feel like it or not the
scriptures declare that the dragon was
wroth with the woman and went to make
war against the remnant of her seed and
them that keep the Commandments of God
and have the testimony of Jesus Christ
that will read that way every time you
open that Bible that war is on it is
on always and so we have to keep that
attitude and one day a man told me a
story about
this sister that was getting ready to
walk down the hill and she saw a
snake and the snake was there and the
snake said um where you going she says
I'm going down the hill snake says well
it's cold can you pick me up and uh give
me a lift down the hill says what you're
a
snake you go I can't pick you up I pick
you up you're gonna bite me he says yeah
but it's cold out here and I don't have
anybody with me to help me I don't have
any way of getting down the hill I just
need to get down the hill I mean you're
a Christian you're a good person and you
can help me out can't you says yeah but
you're a snake he says yeah but it's
cold and I don't have any help you see
what's happening he's playing on her
emotions and compromising and turning
away from one established fact this is a
snake so she picks him up starts walking
down the hill what
happens the snake bit
her she says you bit me I showed you
kindness I showed you Mercy I was
carrying you down the hill I was helping
you there was nobody else there for you
I was there for you he says yeah but you
knew the whole time from the very start
that I was a snake you knew that when
you picked me up you said it what am I
trying to say Saints we know that we are
of God little children and the whole
world lith in
wickedness we are to be ruok hakes we
are to be set apart Sanctified for the
Master's use he has a plan and a purpose
for your life do not allow anyone or
anyone anybody to cause you to be
turning to the left or to the right in
fact that is exactly what God Said to
Joshua next and I want you to consider
as God is saying these things to Joshua
what has just happened in Joshua's life
Israel's greatest leader has just passed
away he's just lost Moses grief is in
his heart somebody grief is in his heart
and yet God saying to him in Joshua 1: 6
and 7 listen to what the Lord says he
says be strong and of a good courage for
on this people shalt thou divide for an
inheritance the land which I swear unto
their fathers to give them only be thou
strong and very courageous that thou
mayest observe to do according to all
the law which Moses my servant commanded
thee turn not from it to the right hand
or to the left that thou mayest Prosper
whether soever thou goest
at even at a time like that the Lord
would stand there and the Lord is
telling him I he he already said earlier
my Moses my servant has died so God was
not ignorant to what was going on in his
life but yet there was a call and a
great call on his life it had nothing to
do with what was going on around him it
had nothing to do with his pain although
God understood it God had made provision
for it and
victory is his who standing here with us
today who's listening today with stuff
going on in and around your life with
struggles and trials there is so much
going on in our world right now to
distract us and to get our minds on well
maybe I can't make because all this
happening and all these people are doing
this I'm hearing about that I'm hearing
about Saints one thing is needful Jesus
said that when he was at the house of
Lazarus Martha and Mary says one thing
is needful and we need to just hold on
to that and stay focused on what this
said the Lord it is
written and we need the power of the
Holy Ghost do not be afraid to seek the
Lord that he might baptize you with the
Holy Ghost and Fire because so much of
this stuff that's happening in this
world right now Pastor Sante spoke this
morning about that manifestation of that
Whirlwind that manifestation that
Miracle that's going to be performed in
order to bring this whole world together
against the people of God and against
the truth of God let me tell you
something we're going to need the holy
ghes to resist that thing there's not
one of us who's smart enough to resist
that thing in our own strength remember
the god that's behind this caus angels
angels to leave their first Abode in
glory you and I who are weak and feeble
and have memories of sin these angels
had no experience with sin one Angel
killed
185,000 one Angel Mighty awesome
creatures have seen and heard things
that you and I have never even imagined
and yet this Celestial being
had the ability to deceive them into
leaving that to come here you and I
stand no chance at all apart from the
the power the grace and the mercy of the
Lord Jesus Christ we can't be playing
with this thing in church let me tell
you some saints this is not something to
play
with we need that baptism of the Holy
Ghost every day we need the spirit of
wisdom and Revelation and the knowledge
of him we need the spirit of grace and
the spirit of Glory the spirit of faith
we need that the spirit of Grace and
supplication that we might learn to stay
on our knees seeking God's facei stay in
prayer wrestle with God In Prayer until
the answer comes wrestle like Jacob
Hallelujah until you get your
breakthrough wrestle till the Lord
touches you in your thigh and breaks
that one strength thing you holding on
to until you limping and let your
weakness become his strength wrestle
with God and do not let go beloved I'm
here to tell you as a living witness he
will come through he will answer I will
never forget it how he came through how
it came through for me you know how long
I was gone 25 years thought I was locked
up for Life thought I was never gonna
get out it wasn't me it wasn't my wit it
wasn't my charm it wasn't my eloquence
or sophistication it was God that
stepped up in that board one day and let
him know look let him go I'll take it
from here I'll take it from here he's
transformed he's changed and I did that
and so I want to encourage somebody
today that's all we're doing we're
seeking to encourage you so here you are
in your now and now I want to say this
to you about now coming to your now
without a point of reference is a
dangerous thing look at this next slide
this was something God gave me this week
as I was thinking about point of
reference and by the way our point of
reference is what God has said and what
God has done nothing else this slide was
a quote that God gave me he said not
maintaining a solid point of reference
makes now a very dangerous place to be
and yet now is all we had not
maintaining a solid point of reference
makes your now a very dangerous place to
be and yet now is all we have and so we
are required we got to in order to make
it have that solid point of reference
which is thus sayith the Lord what thus
sayith the Lord it is written and an
experiential Faith with him listen to me
when we don't come to our now with a
solid point of reference let me tell you
what happens now has a seductive and a
delusional power about it you know what
now has the ability to do when you come
here without a solid point of reference
it has the ability to Blind you to
what's
next when you come to your now without
knowing exactly who you
are how you've been called and what
you've been called to you're liable to
make some decisions right now that'll
set you up for Destruction next and
we'll find ourself in our necks blaming
it all on the devil most people find
their themselves in their Nows and
thinking boy the devil show is trying to
destroy me and take me down but do an
inventory and look back what you did at
your last now your now becomes your next
and so what we want to do is we want to
seek humbly before the Lord see I don't
have time to be bothering you about what
you're doing and all up in your business
unless I can come alongside you and
encourage you and help you because I got
to get my now right come on somebody
that's why the Apostle Paul said we
ought to live quiet lives and mind our
own business check it
out Hallelujah your now becomes very
very dangerous when you come here
without that solid point of reference
which is what thus sayith the Lord now I
want to share one other
thought I noticed this and I and the
Lord this week as I was kind of just
meditating on this took me back to
something that was
mentioned something that was mentioned
in John's call Paul call and Jeremiah
you know what that was there was one
common denominator in all of them yeah
they were all called and yeah they all
Sanctified and set apart but look this
next slide it was the womb and each of
those texts they mentioned the womb Paul
said when God separated me from my
mother's womb Jeremiah said the Lord
said to Jeremiah before I formed thee in
the belly and before I bought thee out
of the womb he said to John he would be
filled he said to Zechariah regarding
John he will be filled with the holy
ghost from his mother's womb why mention
him
womb what's so significant about
that here is your strong point of
reference beloved here's what God is
trying to do he's trying to Anchor Us in
such a way because every one of us has
come out of the
womb every one of us has come out of the
womb and so what God is saying is I
called you from the womb I know that
from the womb until now a whole lot has
happened but nothing between the time I
knew you and formed you and called you
can change what I have said about you
the counsel of the Lord that shall stand
the psalmist said it is the counsel of
the Lord that shall stand I said this at
the beginning of this message it the God
who spoke planets into existence they
there right now at his word at his
command they stood fast and God has a
call on your life
he knew you and me before the foundation
of the world that call Will Stand your
trials are not big enough to take a to
negate that call the gifts and callings
of God are irre irrevocable Apostle Paul
said to the Romans in Romans chapter 11
vers 29 they are irrevocable because
when he speaks something happens when he
speaks something happens your enemy and
my enemy knows that 1 Thessalonians
chapter 2:13 says that the word of God
worketh effectually in them that believe
all he's got to do is get us to stop
focusing on that point of reference
God's word what God has said and all we
have to do Saints is just hold on to
what thus sayith the Lord it will
accomplish what he sent it forth to do I
don't have to do it and you don't have
to do it but from the womb until now a
whole lot has happened come on somebody
you said when when I when when I when
it's all over I'm gonna put on my robe
and tell the story that was the song we
heard at the beginning of this message
put on my RO what story you tell it's a
lot to be told in these stories Saints
ain't it there's a lot to be told in
these stories amen I love the slide the
brothers put the slide up uh you can see
the womb from John the Baptist filled
with the Holy Ghost even from his
mother's womb Paul separated me from my
mother's womb and Jeremiah said before I
God said to Jeremiah before I formed the
in the belly I knew thee and before thou
camest forth out of the womb I
Sanctified thee from the oh look at
this look at God took it a step further
with jerem Jemiah he said not just the
womb he said before I formed thee in the
belly I knew thee you know what God is
doing he wants to take it even deeper
Saints he wants to make us like a tree
planted by the rivers of water remember
what the psalmist said let's go have a
look let's go have a look at Psalms 139
and it was only through the fact that
when God starts talking to Jeremiah he
says before I even formed you in the
belly I knew you watch what the psalmist
said in Psalm 139 here he says for thou
Hast possessed my Reigns thou has
covered me in my mother's womb I will
praise thee for I am fearfully and
wonderfully made look at the psalmist he
knew that he was anatomically designed
to go forward somebody marvelous are thy
works and that my soul knoweth right
well my substance was not hid from thee
when I was made in secret and curiously
wrought in the lowest parts of the earth
Thine Eyes did see my substance yet
being unperfect and in thy book all my
members were written which in continuous
were fashioned when as yet there was
none of them do you see what the Lord is
saying here he taking which one of y'all
can sit here and say like in verse 15 my
subance was not hid from thee when I was
made in secret and curiously rot in the
lowest parts of the
earth curiously rot in the lowest parts
of the
earth we know that each one of us was
formed in our mother's womb and that's
where we came from but God is trying to
direct our minds further back curiously
rought in the lowest part of the earth
we know what Romans chapter uh uh 5
verse2 says through one man sented into
the world and therefore death passed
upon all men so all have sinned we know
that we inherited that from Adam but God
is saying to us here when I was forming
that first man in the
earth I had Terry on my mind I had a
plan for Ivor I had a plan for at tante
I had a plan for Clint I had a plan for
amra I got a plan for Jojo I was I got
something that I'm going to do with
Jackie and Danny I got something I'm
going to do with Michelle and Marisella
I got something I'm gonna do in this
life and I'm putting it together maesa
I'm putting it together Elder Robert E
plant right now in his mind listen to me
in my
mind let me take this back a little bit
further in Jeremiah I don't have a slide
for this in Jeremiah 17:12 the Bible
says a glorious High Throne from the
beginning was the place of our
Sanctuary what in the world is this
Prophet saying a glorious High Throne
from the beginning was the place of our
Sanctuary you know I have thoughts on my
mind and if y'all want come by sometime
and help me I forget something you know
a thought in my little finite mind is
just drifting and wafting through from
time to time by the grace of God I can
remember some things I important thing
Hallelujah I thank God for healing my
mind from the drugs and the alcohol and
the foolishness and now he's given me
the ability to to maintain to to to to
retain his word I thank God for that
best thing ever happened to my mind was
the word of the Living
God but what's a thought in the infinite
mind of the most high
God y'all need to think about that for a
minute what's a thought look like in
that
mind and you and I were on his mind even
then curiously wrought in the lowest
parts of the Earth the psalmist said and
you know this psalmist was not actually
there when God was forming Adam or was
he he was in the heart of God and that
is our point of reference saints that is
where we come from why do you think he
said to Peter he has begotten us again
until alive later
hope go look it up in First Peter he's
begotten us again unto a lively hope our
place is in God this world is not our
home and from that time the beginning it
takes the Holy Ghost to take us and root
us this way and I pray to God that he
will root this word this Revelation this
truth this reality in our hearts and
minds and Spirits so that we can go
through whatever we got to go through
see that's what'll make you a rider of
the storm but because you know when
Jesus said let's cross over to the other
side he didn't say nothing about the
storm that you they was going to get but
they was definitely going to get to that
other side because he spoke it ah
somebody he didn't say nothing about the
bills you was gonna F he didn't say
nothing about the sickness and the
disease he didn't say nothing about the
sorrow and the Heartbreak and the
heartache mothers he didn't tell you
about how them years your son was gonna
send him spend in prison but God when
God speaks a word you know my mother
she's going to watch this later but
she's at church right now but she going
to watch this later my mother one day
when I had reefa in my drawer she didn't
even know about one day when I had doing
all kind of stuff full of the devil my
mama said to me you know the Lord showed
me you're gonna
preach and I thought my mom was crazy
when she said
that and here we are today
now now the word of the Lord will not
fail Joshua said on his death bed he
said to the Israel he called them to him
he said y'all know y'all know the way
the Lord done let us and not one word he
has spoken has fallen to the ground you
want a strong point of reference Saints
put your hope in the word of the Living
God put your hope in the Living God
that's the only thing when the
foundations of the world are being
shaken right now in Hebrews chapter 12
he told us he says God shaken everything
right now Heaven and Earth so the only
thing that can remain will remain and
that is the kingdom of God that we are
receiving right now that we're entering
into right now put your hope in
something that lasts don't be in don't
be fighting and arguing and debating and
and and worrying and wrestling over
things that don't satisfy and things
that are not going to last store up your
Treasures in glory where rust and moth
and can't come in and eat it and take it
away come on somebody I don't know who
the Lord is talking to up in here don't
find yourself in church arguing and
fussing and fighting over little old
stuff that don't even make no difference
you too big for that you bigger than
that your call is greater than that God
has called you now to be a light unto
the world Saints we're too big for some
of the stuff we find oursel caught up in
come on somebody I was locked up and
thought I was never going to get out of
there that's basically what God told the
prison he said look he too big for this
now it's over this he's over this now
when he came here he needed to be here
Terry don't need to be here no more I
got him I'll take it from here come on
somebody come on somebody and by the way
in order for me to do what I do I need
you I need your prayers Saints need your
prayers our leaders need your prayers
people out there struggling need your
help right now somebody some some leader
who thought you you could never make it
you thought you could never come through
what you're going through God need the
kingdom of God needs you somebody needs
you God has a call on your life there's
something for you to do that nobody else
has been called to do
Saints come on somebody lift up your
head and walk lift up your head and give
God glory in this place today today
Hallelujah a strong point of reference
all
right well I want to I want to share one
final thought before we go glory to God
Amen I see you in the chat Saints glory
to God glory to God we all have been
called to do this thing together let's
do it because God gonna bring us on
through somebody huh haven't you read
Heaven's diary haven't you listened to
Heaven's diary did not your heart burn
within you as you listen to that come on
somebody H Allelujah well there one
other thing I was thinking about and um
for a minute there I thought I wasn't
going to get to it but I do want to
share this about
now this is important this is this
aspect of this message about now is very
important in Luke's gospel in Luke
chapter
14 verses
12-13 there was a supper and Jesus was
invited to it and when he was at that
supper he decided I need I need to I
need to bring something to y'all
attention here he he he says then said
he also unto him that b him that invited
him to the dinner he says when when thou
makest a dinner or a supper call not thy
friends nor thy Brethren neither thy
Kinsmen nor thy Rich neighbors lest they
also bid thee again and a recompense be
made thee but when thou makest a feast
call the poor the man the lame the
blind he goes on to say yeah he says and
and thou shalt be blessed for for they
cannot recompense thee for Thou shalt be
recompensed at the resurrection of the
just Hallelujah and when one of them
that sat at meat with him heard these
things he said unto them blessed is he
that shall eat bread in the kingdom of
God come back to the screen I didn't
even catch this myself when I first read
it I missed what was being said
here this
brother had his mind on the resurrection
which is a blessing he had his mind on
the future but he was right there in his
now and Jesus was telling him something
about his now and he thought it would be
most convenient to redirect his
attention away from his now to the
Future blessing but that future blessing
will be his next depending on what he do
with his now you see we have a
responsibility before us right now and
we want to do our best now we don't want
to divert attention away from our
responsibilities right here right now
yeah we want to get to Glory yeah we
want to see Jesus yeah we want to put on
our robe and tell the story but what the
story gonna say about what you did when
you was at that dinner did you invite
the poor in the main in there what's the
story going to be what is the story
going to be we are in the now writing
the story right now Saints we're writing
our story look at what the spirit of
Prophecy said about this this is what
made this really burning in my heart is
when I read what the testimony had to
say what sister white said about this in
Christ's object lesson was beautiful she
says that uh the Pharisee was not
thinking of his own Fitness for heaven
but of what he had hoped to enjoy in
heaven his remark was designed to turn
away the minds of the guests at the
feast from the subject of their
practical Duty he thought to carry them
past the present life to the remote time
of the resurrection of the
just amen amen I thought that was
beautifully put and it really was I
found that a convicting when I first
read that and I thank God for the
warning but you know if one thing is
through true the exact opposite is also
true you see there's some people in this
life who've never had anything there's
some people in this life who've always
known pain and struggle and
heartache there's some people in this
life who's who whose circumstances make
it appear as if they had never had
anything to offer or somebody in this
life your pain might be so bad that all
you can think about look at I just I got
to get out of
here I need to get out of here we need
to get the glory and I want to say this
to you maintaining a powerful point of
reference knowing that you have been
called and separated Sanctified and set
apart by the ru cadesh for a purpose
knowing that God has called you to be
his sign knowing that he has provided
for you everything you will need to
fulfill your PL your call in this life
will give you the hope and the
confidence that you ain't got to look
past your now to the Future you can
stand right in the middle of your storm
you can stand the Bible said that our
children will talk with the enemy in the
gate we will press the battle to the
gate we will look in the face of our
trials look at the face of our Mountain
even if we got to stare death in the
face and declare that our God is more
than able to deliver us out of this and
even if he don't we will not bow down to
anything other than the Lord Jesus
Christ somebody ought to give him praise
and glory in here today our God is that
good that when we maintain our point of
reference we will not be distracted from
our present Duty in our now our present
blessings in our now I love what the
word of God says in 1 Corinthians uh
chapter 10:13 it says that there has no
temptation taken us but that which is
common to man no matter if it seems
unusual no matter how unique your
struggle might seem the Bible says it's
common to man somebody somewhere and
going through what you're going through
such is common to man but God is
faithful who will not suffer you to be
tempted above that which you are able
but will
with the Temptation also make a way of
Escape that you might be able to BU
it it's one thing to be in a situation
thinking Ain't No Way Out
psychologically that could drive you
crazy and all you can think about is
getting out but when you there knowing
that you got the victory right in the
middle of it and knowing that with the
Temptation there's a way out and all
instead of me focusing on the problem I
want to look at the way out and see is
it gonna benefit the kingdom of God for
me to get out of here or just stay put
and be a blessing to somebody when you
know that you have been called
Sanctified and set apart when you know
that God has called you to be a sign and
a Wonder there's a purpose for your life
no matter what you find yourself
in no matter what situation we're in
we're the shine Saints now and so thank
God for the word today I
pray if someone is watching right now
and you'll say Lord I want to step into
my now I want to stand up in my now I
want to get a point of reference in my
life that overrules anything going on in
and around my life I want to be rooted
and anchored in what you have said what
you have done what you have accomplished
and I just saw it in your word Lord
before the foundation of the world you
knew
me if that is you today put your one in
the
chat put your one in the chat as an Act
of Faith Hallelujah said look Lord
wow even me even you even you today I
don't care what situation you're in
right now I don't care what the
circumstance is right now the god of the
Bible is more than able and he's greater
and the purpose and call on your life is
greater than anything you will go
through from the
[Music]
womb to the
Grave come on somebody he is Alpha and
Omega there before the womb
and there and
Beyond see the ones in the chat
Hallelujah Lord look at your people God
look at your people see their hearts see
their lives step into their homes Lord
step into their minds step into their
now Lord in Jesus name and help them to
know that Victory is theirs
now strength is theirs now God purpose
is theirs now Lord because of what you
have done because of what you have said
righteousness Hallelujah Lord your word
says that you came to declare the
righteousness of God in Christ Jesus and
you have never spoken something and it
didn't happen righteousness by faith in
you and what you can do and so we just
give you glory today Father we rest in
you today we praise you today God may
this word be alive in the hearts and the
minds of your people may somebody's
Direction and course and life be changed
forever after this day God in Jesus
mighty name and Lord we give you all of
the glory all of the honor and all of
the praise for what you have done what
you are now doing and what we know and
have confidence you will continue to do
in the future and Hereafter in Jesus
glorious name amen amen
Saints so come and join us on the
Afterglow we love you the link will be
in the chat sister Jerry will be hosting
our Afterglow today we know will be fire
and so we just want to thank you we want
to say we love all of you um pastor and
first lady we love you for the vision
for allowing us to uh just come and and
hear the word of God and to discover who
and what he has called and created us to
be thank God so much for y'all we will
not cease to pray for you and long for
you in Jesus
name
amen thank you for joining us today if
this is your first time worshiping with
us please check out our website at
Living mana. Church we are not just here
for Sabbath service we have weekly
programming too that covers mental
health physical health weekly prayer
service Financial Health and proving the
existence of God it is our desire that
our programming will continue to bless
you please continue to pray for us as we
fulfill God's mission to go into all the
world with the Gospel of Jesus Christ
[Music]
e